<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>My Radiant You (MyRadiantU) on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/my-radiant-you-myradiantu/</link><description>Recent content in My Radiant You (MyRadiantU) on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 06:50:50 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/my-radiant-you-myradiantu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>All I Know</title><link>http://example.org/song/2876-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_All_I_Know/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 06:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2876-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_All_I_Know/</guid><description>[C] I Left my home on a Sunday Hear the church bells ringing [Am] Got in my car started driving Driving till the end of road [C] I&amp;#39;ll send my love to you baby From a thousand miles away [Am] It&amp;#39;s like the water is rising And sky&amp;#39;s about to break All I [C] know You made me for a [Am] reason All I [F] know I find myself on my [G] knees again And now you want me to [C] stay I know you want me to [Am] stay Hey, hey!</description></item><item><title>Ar kuģiem un lidmašīnām</title><link>http://example.org/song/2874-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_Ar_Kugiem_Un_Lidmasinam/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:33:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2874-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_Ar_Kugiem_Un_Lidmasinam/</guid><description>Ar kuģiem un lidmašīnām es atgriežos pie tevis, mīļā. Kalnā uguns deg un nav strīds – nāc man līdz. Un miglā notrīs lapas, nodreb mums sirds – nāc man līdz, un neliec man vairs vienam ai-ai-aiziet – nāc man līdz. Kad viss jau būs beidzies, mēs aizvērsim vārtus un durvis ciet. Brāl, kur tu steidzies, neaizej projām, tu paliec viens. Tu paliec viens, tu paliec viens. Neaizej projām, tu paliec viens.</description></item><item><title>Going All the Way</title><link>http://example.org/song/2877-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_Going_All_The_Way/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2877-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_Going_All_The_Way/</guid><description>Take of my shoes I kneal in the dirt I give you keys to my kingdom of hurt This crown is just a faux refflection Tonight you are my only affection I was born to be with you I was born to give it back to you Light up a match and set it on fire Burn up the heart of this righteous liar This prayer is stuck on my lips Can you hear me?</description></item></channel></rss>