<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Ēnas on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/%C4%93nas/</link><description>Recent content in Ēnas on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 11:49:52 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/%C4%93nas/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ir viss savādāk</title><link>http://example.org/song/3168-Enas_-_Ir_Viss_Savadak/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 11:49:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3168-Enas_-_Ir_Viss_Savadak/</guid><description>Skatoties tevī, es skatos uz sevi, Un nav pat neviena, ko pierunāt, Un nav pat neviena, jo tevis nav klāt . Aizverot tevi, es iegrimstu sevī, Jo tu neesi šeit un nav pat tā Visa, kam rīts ir atspulgā . Var jau būt nav tā, ka tas sāp, Var jau būt ir viss savādāk . Un tad melo pats tu sev, Tverot to, kā sen vairs nav . Palaid prom un dodies tālāk!</description></item><item><title>Always</title><link>http://example.org/song/3180-Enas_-_Always/</link><pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 11:30:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3180-Enas_-_Always/</guid><description>I tried to find an answer in every thing you said no emptiness in all those dreams that we both had made I’m running down those streets and the sky is crashing on me is that satisfaction for you to show how brave you are .. don’t run away don’t break me down ‘cause I’ve always loved you And I always will .. and I .. sometimes I think that your mind is acting against the feelings in your heart I know I’m not a perfect person but at least I’m true to myself every night in my dreams you are there – so close one thing I know for sure if you will need me I’ll be there by your side .</description></item><item><title>Candy</title><link>http://example.org/song/3152-Enas_-_Candy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2017 14:15:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3152-Enas_-_Candy/</guid><description>G How can people speak about F Something they really don&amp;#39;t know G They think it&amp;#39;s so smart to tell F About problems they never had G But sometimes it&amp;#39;s better to talk F Than do nothing at all G So let&amp;#39;s listen to each other F And turn these things to good Piedz.: G You said your life is not F So sweet as candy is G F And that&amp;#39;s why you&amp;#39;re drug addict G F Now it&amp;#39;s good, but after some time C F My friend - your life will be G So painful like hell G In your life are lots of days F When you have to choose G And it&amp;#39;s same point to live your life F With or without drugs G So no one can make you do F Something you don&amp;#39;t want to G You live your life only once F So it&amp;#39;s in your hands Piedz.</description></item><item><title>Ar skaistām frāzēm</title><link>http://example.org/song/2575-Enas_-_Ar_Skaistam_Frazem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 14:24:55 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2575-Enas_-_Ar_Skaistam_Frazem/</guid><description>[C] Kāds no mums nav patiess. [F] Vai savādāk var būt? [C] Daudz sapņu prāts noliedz, [F] Tos zaudējot, sirds lūst [C] Tad pēkšņi viens var pateikt [F] Viss beidzies, kā būs - tā būs. [C] Tā zvaigzne kādreiz izdziest, [F] Tai mirklī pagaist it viss. Kad [F] pamanām to, tad [G] izrādās, Cik [C] daudz neizteiktas [Am] sajūtas Un [F] krāsas, tās pārvērš [G] pelēkās, Grib [C] nokļūt, kur tām [Am] vajag būt.</description></item><item><title>Beautiful Morning</title><link>http://example.org/song/431-Enas_-_Beautiful_Morning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/431-Enas_-_Beautiful_Morning/</guid><description>Intro: D Verse 1 D Bm dream is almost gone .. but I’m still dreamy D Bm what a beautiful life .. when you are sleepi’n D Bm it’s nearly 09.00 AM .. sombody screamin’ D Bm streets already full .. such a wonderful morning Chorus G Bm what a beautiful morning .. funny faces all around G D what a beautiful morning .. please smile for awhile G Bm what a beautiful morning .</description></item></channel></rss>