<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>eng on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/tags/eng/</link><description>Recent content in eng on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 16:08:43 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/eng/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Lantern</title><link>http://example.org/song/4924-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Lantern/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 16:08:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4924-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Lantern/</guid><description>Gm Em There was a lantern, hung in a tree So full of fear, it could have been me Dream tangerine, showed us the way I kissed a girl, I remember this day I remember the summers As we sing in the fall Happy to be with you, Want to take you all Sending love to the moon boy From the birds of our hands Sending love to the moon boy From the marching band Good spirit come, with the queen of clowns Take us for a ride, on a magic bus Walkman and watchmen, they had a fight Walkman beat the watchmen Now the bus takes flight I remember the summers As we sing in the fall Happy to be with you, Want to take you all Sending love to the moon boy From the birds of our hands Sending love to the moon boy From the marching band.</description></item><item><title>Cherry Absinthe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3469-Edgars_Kreilis_McKreilis_-_Cherry_Absinthe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3469-Edgars_Kreilis_McKreilis_-_Cherry_Absinthe/</guid><description>I don’t remember A lot of things But the one thing I remember Is the last night of December I didn’t notice You were around How can I be so lifted At the same time feel so twisted? Oooh! I’m not fluent But the language of our love Takes me higher and above Oooh! How do you do it? ‘Cos the language of our love Takes me higher and above Oooh!</description></item><item><title>Cutting the Wire</title><link>http://example.org/song/3466-Samanta_Tina_-_Cutting_The_Wire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3466-Samanta_Tina_-_Cutting_The_Wire/</guid><description>Oooo! Oooo! O! O! Oooo! Oooo! O! O! Oooo! Oooo! O! O! What if I Did not pick up High and dry With no heads up Baby Tell me there&amp;#39;s another way to see this You played me Once what a huge mistake But now it&amp;#39;s twice Don&amp;#39;t give a f*ck I won&amp;#39;t call you Sooo don&amp;#39;t pick up the phone Noooo explaining Noooo excuses I won&amp;#39;t call you Sooo don&amp;#39;t pick up the phone Oooo!</description></item><item><title>Awe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3463-Laime_Pilniga_-_Awe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3463-Laime_Pilniga_-_Awe/</guid><description>I remember when The dream was over I felt kinda sad And now I feel so odd I need to get there back now Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, lookin’ for place to hide from you I went to my childhood place Climbed in my favourite tree in black and white Saw my beloved ones watchin’ Jim and Kurt Playin’ badminton and both them won I felt uplifted and so I flew Over the hills and the morning dew I felt so alive long ago Don’t know where I’m going but I have to go Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, looking for place to hide from you Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, looking for place to hide from you Ah, I got a secret Ah, I got a secret to hold Ooh, ooh Ooh, ooh, I got a secret I got a secret to hold</description></item><item><title>Fire</title><link>http://example.org/song/3447-Double_Faced_Eels_-_Fire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3447-Double_Faced_Eels_-_Fire/</guid><description>I’ve got a fire burning deep inside Illuminates my way when there’s no light Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire Never was the type to fit in / Least likely to succeed Never was the type to listen / Always marching to my own beat Never had a doubt in my mind / Ain’t got no quit in me All I’ve got’s a burning hunger / cuts and bruises to remind me Learned from my pain and heartache / turned all that into fuel All of the rage that I felt / yeah, I put in my rear-view Feel tall like the highest tower / there ain’t no stopping me All I’ve got’s a burning hunger / and voices in my head, they’re singing I’ve got a fire burning deep inside Illuminates my way when there’s no light Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire Stood on the edge of darkness / Felt my spirit breaking Thought that there&amp;#39;s no going back / My girl, my friends and family saved me Don&amp;#39;t know if I picked the right path / Or where it&amp;#39;s leading me All I&amp;#39;ve got&amp;#39;s a burning hunger / and voices in my head, they&amp;#39;re singing Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire I’ve got a fire, burning deep inside, a fire burning deep inside I’ve got a fire, burning deep inside, a fire burning deep inside I’ve got a fire</description></item><item><title>Listen to the way that I breathe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3445-Laika_Upe_-_Listen_To_The_Way_That_I_Breathe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3445-Laika_Upe_-_Listen_To_The_Way_That_I_Breathe/</guid><description>You keep lying Eyes glued to the ceiling I keep scratching Until you come falling down from the plaster What a disaster, your stare is red Your hands are sewn to the bed The liquids that we used Are floating safe in a drain Now flush them from your brain Listen to the way that I breathe My heartbeat, the way I speak Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Listen to the way that I breathe My heartbeat, the way I speak Face the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Are you back Or just planning to attack The words you speak are sweet But somehow I see through you The demons still hold true!</description></item><item><title>Fireworks</title><link>http://example.org/song/3443-Alekss_Silvers___-_Fireworks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3443-Alekss_Silvers___-_Fireworks/</guid><description>Lying in my bed of silence Know you’re gonna come tonight Thinking of the consequences Asking why Wonder if I think about you Want to know if I still care You’re the one who wants it over But we’re here This love’s incomplete It never will be But it hurts me to breathe All I care for Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn Look into my eyes and tell me Who you really wanna be Enemies, friends or lovers Who are we Said you’re staying with another But you’re always coming back Tired of being undercover Losing track This love’s incomplete It never will be But it helps me to breathe All I care for Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn This isn’t right (This isn’t right) But you’re safe for tonight (Safe for tonight) Out of sight (Out of sight) Holding me tight (Holding me tight) Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn</description></item><item><title>A Day With Us</title><link>http://example.org/song/3438-Divas_Takas_-_A_Day_With_Us/</link><pubDate>Sat, 05 Jan 2019 17:57:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3438-Divas_Takas_-_A_Day_With_Us/</guid><description>When you feel alone and social media makes you sad Remember about your friends They will make you feel better You are not alone on this winter day You can spend it with us We can do nothing at all at least we&amp;#39;ll be together A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self We know each other well We&amp;#39;ve done so many things together From traveling to snow man building Fun or serious Let&amp;#39;s celebrate Christmas together We&amp;#39;ll waste this day too It&amp;#39;s the only present I need To be with you A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self We&amp;#39;ll watch Christmas movies Sing, eat, laugh and tell stories This is gonna be great To be with you On Christmas day A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self A day wasted on others Is not wasted on one&amp;#39;s self</description></item><item><title>1000 Roses</title><link>http://example.org/song/3291-Monta_Kimene_-_1000_Roses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3291-Monta_Kimene_-_1000_Roses/</guid><description>When nothing happens As I’ve wanted And life has struggled in A place I shouldn’t be I take my favourite ring And put it on my finger Just to be sure If there exist any power helping me recall My strength From earth and ground Where my feet are From earth and ground Where my feet are As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses I found a letter From a man Who used to love me I didn’t know Much about it But with look Of grown eyes I know it was, it was, it was Love from heaven Love from mirror of myself Love from heaven Love from getting out of hell As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses Uh, I know he loves me still Uh, I know he loves me still, still As I lay down I smell the sweetness As I lay down I smell the sweetness As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses</description></item><item><title>Lovers Bliss</title><link>http://example.org/song/3288-Lauris_Valters_-_Lovers_Bliss/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3288-Lauris_Valters_-_Lovers_Bliss/</guid><description>So there is something I really want you to know I love you darling About that I&amp;#39;m sure And when the sun rise Shining on our way Or even rainstorm Listens how we pray We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Standing in crossroads Got that feelin&amp;#39; where to go I&amp;#39;m holding you hand Our hearts are beating strong It is so simple And hard at the same time To love somebody With openly wide heart We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss (Where ever we go) (When ever we want to be together) Where ever we go When ever we want to be together We wanna be together Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss</description></item><item><title>Funny Girl</title><link>http://example.org/song/3274-Laura_Rizzotto_-_Funny_Girl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 18:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3274-Laura_Rizzotto_-_Funny_Girl/</guid><description>Ain’t it funny, ain’t it funny Oh, it all started as a joke But now I’m falling, now I’m falling The punch line is getting old Cause I’ve been keeping to myself For way too long, yeah Ain’t it funny, ain’t it funny I made you laugh every time we spoke I locked my heart in hesitation But somehow, you cracked the code I tore down my walls Wrecked the ceiling Ready to bare it all, but You’re looking at her, she’s looking at you I’m falling apart, what can I do To make you feel that way about me too?</description></item><item><title>Just Fine</title><link>http://example.org/song/3281-Sudden_Lights_-_Just_Fine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 17:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3281-Sudden_Lights_-_Just_Fine/</guid><description>Capo 3 Em Am Em G Em Am Em Em Am All alone in a crowded place Em Everyone on their way G Em Am Em Going nowhere Lawyers beggars and busy businessmen All worshipping some kind of colored Chinese paper Can cut my ears off And pull my eyes out To fit right in The more you think and calculate The more confusion there is To be left The further we go the more we forget What it was all about In the rise It sometimes it annoys to be sane In this insane world, we eat, sleep and reproduce But maybe I will be just fine And I will be just fine</description></item><item><title>Have Fun</title><link>http://example.org/song/3258-Lily_-_Have_Fun/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Jan 2018 20:57:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3258-Lily_-_Have_Fun/</guid><description>You can make a lot of fun You can make a lot of things You can make a lot of wishes ‘cause we are happy people And we live in the free world Come and sing a song with me And we can have fun Come and build your hope with me And we can have fun You can make a lot of fun You can make a lot of things You can make a lot of wishes ‘cause we are happy people And we live in the free world Come and sing a song with me And we can have fun Come and build your hope with me And we can have fun</description></item><item><title>Intoxicating Caramel</title><link>http://example.org/song/3205-Katrina_Gupalo_-_Intoxicating_Caramel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3205-Katrina_Gupalo_-_Intoxicating_Caramel/</guid><description>Intoxicating scent sends wild flashes right in my prudence Agitating dead ends easily crashes I&amp;#39;m ready to dance Sticky caramel in both my ears Buzzing bumble-bee time disappears The feeling I&amp;#39;m 16 Indecently twisty Shakes my misty mind since he kissed me Intoxicating scent sends wild flashes right in my prudence Agitating dead ends easily crashes I&amp;#39;m ready to dance Intoxicating scent sends wild flashes right in my prudence Agitating dead ends easily crashes I&amp;#39;m ready to dance This leaky faucet Oh how can I knock it?</description></item><item><title>Heartbeat 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3138-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat_2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:52:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3138-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat_2/</guid><description>Am I know you told So many times Am So many words In different rhymes Dm C G But I don’t feel the same Am I wasn’t innocent, I know Am And things I did for sure were wrong Dm C G The time has passed so long Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am I’m getting wild when I’m alone Am I learned by heart you&amp;#39;re not my own D C Am But I never asked you to be long Am Your my desire and my pain Am But all the battles are in vain D C G You mean more than anything to me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me F You’re the one I need Am You’re the air that I breathe C Don’t throw my heart away G I want you to stay Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat</description></item><item><title>Love Injected 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3137-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected_2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3137-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected_2/</guid><description>Gm | Gm | Eb | Cm7 Gm You bring Gm/Bb The light Eb To Cm7 My darkest side, babe. Gm The day, Gm/Bb The night Eb Split Cm7 To cure the sight, oh. Gm You care, Gm/Bb You animate, Eb You guard me bare, Cm7 Bring up the heart rate. Gm Your love F Eb Revives my soul F Bb And I know Bb You&amp;#39;ll choose it whole F Eb Cm7 Overall.</description></item><item><title>Line 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</guid><description>E Ebm I&amp;#39;m going round in circles Abm F# And the door&amp;#39;s wide open E Ebm Boy I still wanna see you Abm F# Days go by, I&amp;#39;m still hoping, hoping E Where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? F# E Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? E Ebm You told me to move on Abm Searching now for somebody else F# E Ebm But baby, tell me how will I find it?</description></item><item><title>I Wish I Knew</title><link>http://example.org/song/3106-Linda_Leen_-_I_Wish_I_Knew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3106-Linda_Leen_-_I_Wish_I_Knew/</guid><description>Everytime you’re walking by I feel like flying high But then I realize: The blue is in your eyes Telling you how much I care makes you stop, sit and stare So then I walk away and you don’t make me stay Your hesitation seems too long So in all confusion I wrote you this song I wish I knew what should I do To make the sun shine, to make you all mine Here is my heart, don’t break it apart Look in my eyes and read: It’s you that I need My mind says stop to dream and row another stream And walk another land and try to understand My heart beats only for you, and yours?</description></item><item><title>For You My Friends</title><link>http://example.org/song/3103-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_For_You_My_Friends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3103-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_For_You_My_Friends/</guid><description>One day you’ll understand that you are alone And the world around you, cold and firm like stone And that’s the miracle, you’ll need a real friend To whom you do not have to lie and to pretend And that’s the miracle, you’ll need a real friend To whom you do not have to lie and to pretend You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You’ll see all people in another way In your life, it won’t be a hard and heavy day And that’s the important day, you’ll need a real friend The tell that you are tired, to lie and to pretend And that’s the important day, you’ll need a real friend The tell that you’re tired, to lie and to pretend You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile</description></item><item><title>I Might Be the One</title><link>http://example.org/song/3099-Madara_Celma_-_I_Might_Be_The_One/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3099-Madara_Celma_-_I_Might_Be_The_One/</guid><description>You may close, close every door if you dare You may turn, turn out the lights And pretend you’re not there You can try to forget about me, but please Stop before you do ‘Cause I might be your only shelter Might be the one who always stands for you All you have to do is call my name in silence And I will run to you like I have wings I don’t and I won’t believe that you’re gonna leave Look at me, stay with me Feel the flame burning in me, in your eyes Still I can see how much you need me Please, stop before you go ‘Cause I might be your only shelter Might be the one who always stands for you All you have to do is call my name in silence And I will run to you like I have wings ‘Cause I might be your only shelter Might be the one who always stands for you All you have to do is call my name in silence And I will run to you like I have wings You gave me wings</description></item><item><title>Let's Go Insane</title><link>http://example.org/song/3105-Linda_Leen_-_Lets_Go_Insane/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3105-Linda_Leen_-_Lets_Go_Insane/</guid><description>There’s a place I used to know It was all so beautiful It was only for me and you Would you come into my place? Would you go into my shoes? Would you stand the hard embrace? When I give my heart When I fall in love It will be the same Baby, baby, I wanna be your star Let me hide and fall in your sky Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby, let’s go insane Lay your body next to mine Feel the ground and heaven above Hear the sound of my soul I don’t wanna fight no more I don’t want you to lie Don’t want me to cry, don’t wanna hide When I give my heart When I fall in love It will be the same Baby, baby, I wanna be your star Let me hide and fall in your sky Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby It is true Love you Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby Let’s go insane Baby, baby, I wanna be your star Let me hide and fall in your sky Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby, let’s go insane</description></item><item><title>I Was a Lonely Girl</title><link>http://example.org/song/3098-Linda_Leen_-_I_Was_A_Lonely_Girl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3098-Linda_Leen_-_I_Was_A_Lonely_Girl/</guid><description>I was a girl with an empty space in my heart I was a rock that stands on the empty beach, oh my God I had no home, had no money, had no place to go But, baby, you moved me on I didn&amp;#39;t cry, I didn&amp;#39;t laugh I had two eyes, but I was blind I had no grief, no happiness There was no order neither mess I was always in between humbleness and self-esteem You made me live I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo If you have lived, You don&amp;#39;t want just to exist anymore Here is my heart, boy I know you&amp;#39;ll keep it in warmth You have made me love, Made me hate, too I am thankful to you and, Baby, you moved me I didn&amp;#39;t cry, I didn&amp;#39;t laugh I had two eyes, but I was blind I had no grief, no happiness There was no order neither mess I was always in between humbleness and self-esteem You made me live I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>http://example.org/song/3064-Euphony_-_Home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3064-Euphony_-_Home/</guid><description>There are so many places around the world to see There are so many people to meet, but only she knows how Knows how to make me feel like I am home There are so many colours and blinding lights to see So beautiful and gracious, you know but only she knows how Knows how to make me feel like I am home Thank you for the life you gave me with your heart Thank you for your love Finally I feel like I can really start Spread my wings and fly above my fears There are so many chances to take, but I’m not sure Of disappointment later and what it’s really for, but she Knows how to make me feel like I am home, home Feels like I’m home and I’m home Thank you for the life you gave me with your heart Thank you for your love Finally I feel like I can really start Spread my wings and fly above Time goes by but there’s no place I’d rather be And I hope I found a decent melody For the song to describe how I feel About you, about love, about family Thank you for the life you gave me with your heart Thank you for your love (Thank you for your love) I can feel it’s time Spread my wings and fly above my fears</description></item><item><title>Lions</title><link>http://example.org/song/3092-Lana_Franceska_-_Lions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:23:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3092-Lana_Franceska_-_Lions/</guid><description>Silence When our words will turn to silence We’ll find the beat of love We’ll hear the beat of love Diamonds Will light up the skies and find us What we rushed to lose too fast Thinking that it would just last Lions In our hearts we’ll find our lions They’ll never let us fall They’ll guard the light that brings us home Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, like the lions that we are Sunrise We have dreamed a dream of sunrise When the morning finally comes We’ll hear the call of love Silence When our words will turn to silence We’ll find the call of love We’ll hear the call of love Lions Come and gather all my lions Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, like the lions that we are (Through the night, time by time)</description></item><item><title>Free Your Mind</title><link>http://example.org/song/3082-The_Stones_-_Free_Your_Mind/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3082-The_Stones_-_Free_Your_Mind/</guid><description>Free your mind and stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you No matter if you’re black or white, no No matter even weak or strong Free your mind and your imagination To make the choices of your own It’s up to you, but I’ll be honest We should realise somehow Just be wise and don’t be nervous Make your own decisions now So come on, keep your heart wide open Hot like oven, burning heart First of all we believe in ourselves Ready to go and ready to start Ātri gāju, ātri skrēju Ātru dzīvi dzīvodams Free your mind and stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you No matter if you’re black or white, no No matter even weak or strong Free your mind and your imagination To make the choices of your own Ātri gāju, ātri skrēju Ātru dzīvi dzīvodams Ātri gāju, ātri skrēju Ātru dzīvi dzīvodams Your dreams will come true It’s time to go through For me and for you, oh… Your dreams will come true It’s time to go through For me and for you And for me and for you, hey Free your mind and stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you No matter if you’re black or white, no No matter even weak or strong Free your mind and your imagination To make the choices of your own Ah… Let’s stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you</description></item><item><title>High Heels</title><link>http://example.org/song/3065-Riga_Metro_-_High_Heels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3065-Riga_Metro_-_High_Heels/</guid><description>Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you How ’bout I give you my heart, heart Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy How ’bout I give you my heart, heart Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy Red lips, bitchy look, high heels Is this what will make his heart beat?</description></item><item><title>Magic Years</title><link>http://example.org/song/3070-Lauris_Valters_-_Magic_Years/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3070-Lauris_Valters_-_Magic_Years/</guid><description>When this world is turning and the fire is burning I keep thinking about you, every moment, my love Can we feel much stronger and make it last longer? Flow down in this river while light is coming from above See children growing, I should be glad Is this the best we ever had? I’m looking for signs in the wind I’m looking for signs in the water I’m looking for signs on the ground I’m looking for signs in the fire When this world is turning and the fire is burning I keep thinking about you, every moment, my love Can we feel much stronger and make it last longer?</description></item><item><title>Escape</title><link>http://example.org/song/3079-Crime_Sea_-_Escape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3079-Crime_Sea_-_Escape/</guid><description>Baby, I am so lost in this labyrinth I don’t know where is the way out of here Another animals would get lost in here They’d rather travel back to the stratosphere It’s another planet that is taking control over us Where to hide, where to go, is this even real life? It’s another planet that is taking control over us Where to hide, where to go, is this even real life?</description></item><item><title>Being A Friend</title><link>http://example.org/song/3080-Ruta_Duduma_-_Being_A_Friend/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 08:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3080-Ruta_Duduma_-_Being_A_Friend/</guid><description>Pieces falling That hold us together Chances we take That turn us for better It’s a road that never end And leads to something we call a friend And no matter how far I will know where you are I will never stop being your friend And I never will ‘Cause you’re my friend when I’m down and blue ‘Cause you’re my friend, I can count on you Your heart has turned around and I’m blessed that I know You are my friend, are my friend, I can count on you, ooh… Show them the best of you I’ll make you dare Believe me, when it’s time to go You know I will care And when the time comes for us to part Oh, I really want you to know That no matter how far I will know where you are I will never stop being your friend And I never will, oh… ‘Cause you’re my friend when I’m down and blue ‘Cause you’re my friend, I can count on you Your heart has turned around and I’m blessed that I know You are my friend, are my friend ‘Cause you’re my friend when I’m down and blue ‘Cause you’re my friend, I can count on you Your heart has turned around and I’m blessed that I know You are my friend, are my friend, you are my friend I can count on you</description></item><item><title>Look In The Mirror</title><link>http://example.org/song/3081-Paula_Dukure_-_Look_In_The_Mirror/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 08:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3081-Paula_Dukure_-_Look_In_The_Mirror/</guid><description>All of us have the same goal To drive the road that makes us call man pleased There’s an illusion we believe in That our happiness can be taken away Open up to what is now Take a clear look at what’s going on Is there a reason to smile Or is it time to change for the better? If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror I know I don’t have to wait long Till I’ll be free from this need To have something that gives me relief I’m learning to love life as it is Waiting for the perfect lover Who will come and make my grief go away But I know it’s too much to ask I’ll just deal with my demons alone If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror I know I don’t have to wait long Till I’ll be free from this need To have something that gives me relief I’m learning to love I know I don’t have to wait long Till I’ll be free from this need To have something that gives me relief I’m learning to love life as it is Ooh yeah yeah… Till I’ll be free from this need I’m learning to love, I’m learning to love I know I don’t have to wait long I’m learning to love (Life as it is)</description></item><item><title>Choices</title><link>http://example.org/song/3089-MARTA_Marta_Grigale_-_Choices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 07:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3089-MARTA_Marta_Grigale_-_Choices/</guid><description>Endless possibilities Different you, different me Lovers make and lovers break Funny how the smallest thing can alter everything Endless possibilities Different you, different me One step here and one step there You are closer now and further than you’ve ever been Every single choice you make Every single step you take The ink you leave’s indelible Choices, choices Every little word you say Every promise that you break The ink you leave’s indelible Choices, choices There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice Endless possibilities Different you, different me You can stay or walk away But you’ll never know for sure how it all would have been Every single choice you make Every single step you take The ink you leave’s indelible Choices, choices There’s always (Choices) There’s always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice</description></item><item><title>Had it all</title><link>http://example.org/song/3017-Chris_Noah_Krists_Indrisonoks_-_Had_It_All/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 12:39:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3017-Chris_Noah_Krists_Indrisonoks_-_Had_It_All/</guid><description>When city lights turned into shadows I found you standing there alone Your jeans were torn your heart was broken You couldn&amp;#39;t get back to your feet No matter were we could find the light We made the shadows turn into light Two different worlds will collide We&amp;#39;ve spent long nights in this town And if i want to take you with me Would you say yes of all for me There is no way back just road ahead us Decisions coming back and forth No matter were we could find the light We made the shadows turn into light Two different worlds will collide We spent long nights in this town we had it all, and i feel so lost We had it all and i feel so lost</description></item><item><title>Brown Eyes And All The Rest</title><link>http://example.org/song/3014-Carnival_Youth_-_Brown_Eyes_And_All_The_Rest/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2017 20:38:52 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3014-Carnival_Youth_-_Brown_Eyes_And_All_The_Rest/</guid><description>Intro(2x) C# G# D# D# C# Ab Bb Bb Db Ab Eb What if I push myself Db Ab Bb What if I try to do it all by myself Db Ab Eb You and I could see for ourselves Db Ab Bb With our brown eyes and all the rest Db Cm My heart&amp;#39;s too old to survive this storm Fm Eb Yours too bold to give a rest Db Cm So I&amp;#39;ll just try to do my best Fm Eb And let the time do the rest Chorus Db C Fm And let the storm salt the sea Ab Or perform a wicked heresy Bbm C Fm To our hearts and to our minds Ab I&amp;#39;ll be there with you Stay calm Db Ab Eb Eb Db Ab Bb Bb Db Ab Eb I would never dare to look at you Db Ab Bb For the fear you would see me through Db Ab Eb Cause love and care is that made my heart Db Ab Bb Cause love and care is that tore it apart Db Cm My heart&amp;#39;s too old to survive this storm Fm Eb Yours too bold to give a rest Db Cm So I&amp;#39;ll just try to do my best Fm Eb And let the time do the rest Db C Fm And let the storm salt the sea Ab Or perform a wicked heresy Bbm C Fm To our hearts and to our minds Ab I&amp;#39;ll be there with you Stay calm Db C Fm And let the storm salt the sea Ab Or perform a wicked heresy Bbm C Fm To our hearts and to our minds Ab I&amp;#39;ll be there, but you stay Fm Fm Eb Eb Db C Fm And let the storm Ab Bbm Take us home C Take us home Fm Ab Db C Fm And let the storm Ab Bbm Take us home C Fm Take us home Db Ab Eb And let the storm salt the sea (take us home) Db Ab Bb Or perform heresy (take us home) Db Ab Eb To our hearts and to our minds Db Ab Bb Db Your brown eyes and all the rest</description></item><item><title>Here We Go</title><link>http://example.org/song/3006-PeR_-_Here_We_Go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 12:46:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3006-PeR_-_Here_We_Go/</guid><description>Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Ladies and Gentlemen, I need a starlight &amp;#39;Cause I never had a day without a fight I slid through the darkness, it took me to a height Of a lonesome, cold and never ending night I&amp;#39;m the man on the moon, call me Andy Kaufman There are demons inside me but I&amp;#39;m stomp&amp;#39;em I know I can be an unstoppable force I try, me, let me take a walk on the bright side Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly A lot of thoughts in my head keep pulling me down So many guests in my house I could not notice the sound Of the doorbell telling they&amp;#39;re about to come I&amp;#39;m surrounded by problems, I got to run (But no) I keep pulling myself up (But no) I keep pulling myself up I&amp;#39;m on a mission to fulfill my vision All day, everyday, never ever, ever give up Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly</description></item><item><title>Beautiful Song</title><link>http://example.org/song/3004-Anmary_-_Beautiful_Song/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 18:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3004-Anmary_-_Beautiful_Song/</guid><description>Intro: F C G Am F C G Am Am Am I was born in distant 1980 C G the year that Irish Johnny Logan won F C/Am thirty years ago, they still remember F so dream away C today&amp;#39;s the day G Am I&amp;#39;m singing out my song Am When I join this grand parade of winners C G and we&amp;#39;ve made this song a worldwide hit F C/Am I will buy oh my own mike to sing in F and all the jobs C I&amp;#39;ve had before G Am I&amp;#39;m surely gonna quit F C G Am Beautiful song is on the radio, is in the tv shows and plays on and on F C G Am beautiful song that everybody hums and everybody loves Am My Mom said I&amp;#39;d grow up to be a singer C G And Daddy smiled when gave me my guitar F C/Am I do my best, and I&amp;#39;ll be so much better F C G Am Brightest of the highest and the farthest of the stars Am And on that day when Sir Mick Jagger phones me C G Tell him, please, that I am very busy F C/Am writing brand new songs with Paul McCartney F C G So sorry Mick, I&amp;#39;ll call you back, someday I&amp;#39;ll call Am you back.</description></item><item><title>It's the night</title><link>http://example.org/song/2902-Antra_Stafecka_-_Its_The_Night/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 09:01:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2902-Antra_Stafecka_-_Its_The_Night/</guid><description>Pull the trigger, come closer to me It&amp;#39;s the night night When my heart is burning with no moves It`s the night night I weak in my knees What are you doing to me me It`s the night, come closer to me Gonna get you some way It`s dangerous - danger - dangerous watch out! Do it baby do it baby Let&amp;#39;s play the game I can keep up with you 2x What you need is me near It `s the night night To set you free free It`s the night night Get adrenaline inside for me, me It`s the night night You might be down for this burning love, love, love, love It`s the night night Gonna get you some way It`s dangerous - danger - dangerous watch out!</description></item><item><title>I Hear Your Heart</title><link>http://example.org/song/2895-Cosmos_-_I_Hear_Your_Heart/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2895-Cosmos_-_I_Hear_Your_Heart/</guid><description>In a world that is beeping and blaring Growing louder every day I cover my ears But none of the noise will go away Sirens, Barking dogs Thank God for the one and only sound that turns it around and makes it right I hear your heart Whisprin’ to me No matter where I may happen to be Sending me love and shining it through I hear your heart Can you hear mine too?</description></item><item><title>Blood Runs Quicker</title><link>http://example.org/song/2891-Katrina_Cirule_-_Blood_Runs_Quicker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 10:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2891-Katrina_Cirule_-_Blood_Runs_Quicker/</guid><description>Tryna find good out of everything i do When there’s a negative it always involves you In my chest tryna break through No need to hide it No need to hide it’s true Don’t bring me down Spread across the ground Hoping that you’ll fix me I know you’re bad for me babe But my heart still flickers How can i run from you babe When my blood runs quicker I’m tryna repair the mess That we’re made But it’s hard to be positive When all we ever do is hate You’re in my head screaming my name I’m not gonna lie I’ve been trying to let you fade so Don’t bring me down Spread across the ground Hoping that you’ll fix me I know you’re bad for me babe But my heart still flickers How can i run from you babe When my blood runs quicker</description></item><item><title>Feel the Love</title><link>http://example.org/song/2894-RocknBerries_-_Feel_The_Love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 10:23:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2894-RocknBerries_-_Feel_The_Love/</guid><description>I’m trying to clear the shades behind us I search for way to own your trust They’re coming up, they try to divine us All of we got turn into dust Why can’t you share what you feel? What you’re feelin’? Why can’t you feel the love that i give Why can’t you share with me what you’re feelin’? What you’re feelin’? Why can’t you feel the love that i’m givin’?</description></item><item><title>Dynamite</title><link>http://example.org/song/2885-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_Dynamite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 14:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2885-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_Dynamite/</guid><description>You are setting fires in my name. You invite a moth into the flames. There’s a steep price to pay, But I know that I’ll stay. Your kind of sorcery is dangerous to me — It’s gonna blow us skyscraper high. Your sensuality is stirring something deep, Unless it’s all a trick of the night. My heart is made of dynamite, dynamite! Dynamite, dynamite! Dynamite, dynamite! I should tell myself until I learn.</description></item><item><title>Little Weird</title><link>http://example.org/song/2879-Laura_Lo_-_Little_Weird/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 20:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2879-Laura_Lo_-_Little_Weird/</guid><description>[C] Late night walking [Am] around in this old [F] city [G] [C] Neon lights are [Am] flashing on your [F] perfect skin [G] [C] You don’t even [Am] know that I’m watching your [F] every move [G] Just [C] talking, walking, [Am] laughing, talking - [F] round and round [G] Cause I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes Cause I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes And we [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [C] Acting silly, feeling [Am] infinite You don’t [F] want to go home [G] [C] We don’t mind what the [Am] others say Cause we’re [F] having the best time [G] tonight And I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes And I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes And we [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Floating somewhere in [F] the space [C] Floating somewhere in [G] the space [Am] Floating somewhere in [F] the space [C] Floating somewhere [G] And we [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars</description></item><item><title>All I Know</title><link>http://example.org/song/2876-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_All_I_Know/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 06:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2876-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_All_I_Know/</guid><description>[C] I Left my home on a Sunday Hear the church bells ringing [Am] Got in my car started driving Driving till the end of road [C] I&amp;#39;ll send my love to you baby From a thousand miles away [Am] It&amp;#39;s like the water is rising And sky&amp;#39;s about to break All I [C] know You made me for a [Am] reason All I [F] know I find myself on my [G] knees again And now you want me to [C] stay I know you want me to [Am] stay Hey, hey!</description></item><item><title>Beyond Velvet Skin</title><link>http://example.org/song/2872-Linda_Leen_-_Beyond_Velvet_Skin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 13:20:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2872-Linda_Leen_-_Beyond_Velvet_Skin/</guid><description>Can you see behind the velvet soft skin, hotblooded flesh? what do you feel is beyond ? dig deeper than just hot breath, blood enriched with raw energy fruity taste of my body it’s in the air, yeah will you ever be close enough to see me clearly through your misty eyes but you don’t care, yeah you just go for hot breath, blood enriched with raw energy fruity taste of my body it’s in the air but sin is so tempting</description></item><item><title>Going All the Way</title><link>http://example.org/song/2877-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_Going_All_The_Way/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:26:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2877-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_Going_All_The_Way/</guid><description>Take of my shoes I kneal in the dirt I give you keys to my kingdom of hurt This crown is just a faux refflection Tonight you are my only affection I was born to be with you I was born to give it back to you Light up a match and set it on fire Burn up the heart of this righteous liar This prayer is stuck on my lips Can you hear me?</description></item><item><title>Line</title><link>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</guid><description>I’m going [F] round in [Em] circles And the [Am] door’s wide [G] open Boy I [F] still wanna see [Em] you Days go [Am] by, I’m still hoping, [G] hoping [F] Where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? [G] Tell me, baby, [F] where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? You [F] told me to move [Em] on Searching [Am] now for somebody else But baby, [G] tell me [F] how will I find [Em] it?</description></item><item><title>I'm In Love With You</title><link>http://example.org/song/2868-The_Ludvig_-_Im_In_Love_With_You/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 17:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2868-The_Ludvig_-_Im_In_Love_With_You/</guid><description>[Am] It&amp;#39;s late in the evening [C] And I&amp;#39;m waiting for you [Am] Soon I&amp;#39;ll stop breathing [C] And I blame it on the full moon So [F] darling, please [G] believe I&amp;#39;m in love with [C] you [Am] Leave your shoes at the door [C] I can&amp;#39;t wait no more [Am] We might be too young [C] But I think we&amp;#39;re in love. So [F] darling, please [G] believe I&amp;#39;m in love with [C] you [F] Time flies by [G] your eyes [Am] When I am with you I [C] feel alive</description></item><item><title>Connection Lost</title><link>http://example.org/song/2779-Carnival_Youth_-_Connection_Lost/</link><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 20:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2779-Carnival_Youth_-_Connection_Lost/</guid><description> Dm G F C You power out, out of reach, lost connection between you and me x2 C Dm Searching in your face Am G For something I could believe in C Dm Where are the toothpaste lines I drew Am G While you were asleep C Dm Voice so distant Am G Your message isn&amp;#39;t clear G D# I don&amp;#39;t feel the tears, C I&amp;#39;m water resistant Dm G You power out, out of reach F C Lost connection between you and me Dm G You power out, now I see F C Lost affection, nothing left for me Am G# C You have turned into a note outside my harmony Am G# C You have turned into a note been outside my mind Am G# C No one talks on silent phones, but the picture&amp;#39;s clear Am G# C &amp;#39;Cause you never tell me, you just disappear Dm G You power out, out of reach F C Lost connection between you and me Dm G You power out, now I see F C Lost affection, nothing left for me Dm G You power out, out of reach, F C lost connection between you and me x2</description></item><item><title>Daydream</title><link>http://example.org/song/2748-RocknBerries_-_Daydream/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:46:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2748-RocknBerries_-_Daydream/</guid><description>She’s like a girl from the scene I’m seein&amp;#39; in my dreams Shining in majesty She put her spell on me I am just a guy she&amp;#39;ve never seen Confused and lost in my daydream So fast and imperceptibly She charmed me easily She’s walking over me I’m seeking words to speak My mind plays tricks on me I can see my destiny If I’m too shy or weak Time leaves me in misery I want you to come with me I know we’re meant to be My cards are plain to see Yeah, you are my fantasy I want you to be with me Let’s unite in harmony Cause you’re livin&amp;#39; in my dreams Yeah, you are my ecstasy</description></item><item><title>Better days</title><link>http://example.org/song/2747-RocknBerries_-_Better_Days/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:46:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2747-RocknBerries_-_Better_Days/</guid><description>They told me better days will come So, I’ve been waiting patiently alone Thousands of sunsets on my own Locked up in my silent groan Where are you, my better days? It has been too long I remain tame for the years to come Until you bless me, my better days How long will I whit-stand My time is slipping through the fingers like sand How long will I whit-stand I guess so long, my better days!</description></item><item><title>Down</title><link>http://example.org/song/2746-RocknBerries_-_Down/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:46:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2746-RocknBerries_-_Down/</guid><description>I was lost in the river And the river was your love They say I am a criminal For steeling your taken heart But I don’t give up! Ooh, I just want to be with you, babe Even when the sun goes down I just want to be with you, darling Even when the world goes down Down, down, down... I was lost in the moonlight And the moonlight was your heart They can track me down they can shot me down But the love will stay on the spot Cause I won’t give it up!</description></item><item><title>Footsteps</title><link>http://example.org/song/2745-RocknBerries_-_Footsteps/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:46:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2745-RocknBerries_-_Footsteps/</guid><description>Footsteps in my heart You left them walking away from me Now that we’re apart The loneliness is all I see The bridge is falling down Call your name around and around.. Around You turned your back on me A thousand times before I’m sick and hopeless laying here And praying at your door I don’t need anything But the thing I know for sure I need your love I need your cure Days are running fast Now that I’m away from you Faces come and go But yours the one I’m searching for The places I have been There’s always just an empty scene</description></item><item><title>Funky Vibes</title><link>http://example.org/song/2744-RocknBerries_-_Funky_Vibes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:46:40 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2744-RocknBerries_-_Funky_Vibes/</guid><description>I play my funky music tonight It makes me high it feels so right I play my funky music all night Wanna feel you dancing by my side When the lights are gone You catch my vibes and I Take your soul tonight I play my funky music tonight I wanna see you move your body right Move those legs to the left and right And let me see you freaky tonight When the lights are gone You catch my vibes and I Take your soul tonight</description></item><item><title>Addiction</title><link>http://example.org/song/2743-RocknBerries_-_Addiction/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2016 19:46:37 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2743-RocknBerries_-_Addiction/</guid><description>Too many wise men all around me Sententious thoughts expressed out loud Confusion leads to desperation I find myself down on the ground I know you’re with me Don&amp;#39;t let me down Why do you tease me? I need you To grab me and take me to The only place where I see through The wall of dust in front of view I can’t resist addiction To your presence by my side Love is my obsession All your wills I&amp;#39;ll satisfy Temptation has no limits Release me and make me fly There’s no justice and no mercy No one’s there to cure your pain Human mindless fight for glory Slowly drives me insane</description></item><item><title>As Fast As I Can</title><link>http://example.org/song/2728-The_Black_Pockets_-_As_Fast_As_I_Can/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 14:13:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2728-The_Black_Pockets_-_As_Fast_As_I_Can/</guid><description>Dm7 Fmaj7 I saw her late that summer C Em7/G Midnight runner Dm7 Fmaj7 Not too long till we got closer C Em7/G Got closer Dm7 Fmaj7 Hearts and colors midnight runners C Em7/G Under cover Dm7 C I never needed approval of someone Dm7 Em7 Anyhow, anyway I know Fmaj7 Am7 All my friends say I don’t need her G6 G9 I should leave her Fmaj7 Am7 All my friends say I don’t need her G6 G9 I should leave her as fast as i can As fast as i can As fast as i can She’s a woman that’s taking all my time Eating all my time Wasting days by waiting on sunsets On sunsets I’ll never regret those wasted sunsets I’ll never forgot I never needed approval of someone Anyhow, anyway I know All my friends say I don’t need her I should leave her All my friends say I don’t need her I should leave her as fast as i can As fast as i can As fast as i can</description></item><item><title>Far Away</title><link>http://example.org/song/2587-Laura_Lo_-_Far_Away/</link><pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2016 10:20:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2587-Laura_Lo_-_Far_Away/</guid><description>[F] I wake up in [C] the midnight It’s [G] so quiet (shhh...) so quiet [F] This silience makes me sick [C] I walk alone [G] in the moonlight It’s [E] so quiet (shhh...) so quiet [F] Just me and [G] thousands of stars [F] There i [C] want to be there [G] Between bright [Am] shiny stars [F] On the [C] top of the moon [G] So far [Am] away from here [F] There is nobody [C] simply empty streets [G] It’s so quiet [Am] I can’t believe i’m here [F] Am i dreaming [C] or am i sleeping?</description></item><item><title>Damnation</title><link>http://example.org/song/2574-Catalepsia_-_Damnation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:40:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2574-Catalepsia_-_Damnation/</guid><description>[Am] Look through my [F] mind It’s a [C] world of con[E]fusion [Am] There&amp;#39;s nothing [F] right to see There’s [C] nothing true to [E] feel [Am] Run, I am [F] cursed Your [C] spell won’t [E] save me My [Am] world is dark and [F] bleak My [C] heart is still and [E] cold [Am] Speak to my [F] soul It’s a [C] voice of the non-[E] existent There’s [Am] nothing to [F] understand There’s [C] nothing fair for [E] you [Am] I am too far, too [F] deep You will [C] never reach my [E] soul [Am] Stay away from [F] me You [C] cannot make it [E] real [Am] I’m too close to [F] fall From the [C] heaven of your [E] dream [Am] Say goodbye to me [F] dear I’m [C] leaving you be[E]hind [Am] Look through your [F] mind It’s a [C] world of destruc[E]tion [Am] There’s nothing to [F] memorize There’s [C] nothing bright for [E] me [Am] Speak to your [F] soul It’s a [C] voice of fading [E] prayer [Am] There’s nothing [F] to revive There’s [C] nothing I can [E] change [Am] I am too far, too [F] deep You will [C] never reach my [E] soul [Am] Stay away from [F] me You [C] cannot make it [E] real [Am] I’m too close to [F] fall From the [C] heaven of your [E] dream [Am] Say goodbye to me [F] dear I’m [C] leaving you be[E]hind</description></item><item><title>Cake to Bake</title><link>http://example.org/song/2546-Arzemnieki_-_Cake_To_Bake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2546-Arzemnieki_-_Cake_To_Bake/</guid><description>Capo 1 Intro: F Dm F Dm F I melted the ice of the polar caps Dm Found the raiders of the lost ark C Solved a case for the genius from Baker Street F Helped to clean the Central Park Dm I created the plan for the Chinese wall Gm Went to desert, made it rain Am Swam through a shark tank bloodily F Found Atlantis, by the way C But today F Bb I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Bb Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku G C Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep F I talked to a unicorn the other night Dm Took me up on a lonely star C Did the moonwalk on the milky way F Realized I&amp;#39;ve gone too far Dm So I questioned the law of gravity Gm Put the apple back up to the apple tree Am Ej tu nost: I even learned Latvian F I know it&amp;#39;s so hard to believe C But today F Bb I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Bb Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku G C Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku F Bb We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Am Bb C Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, wait for it F Am Bb C Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, wait for it F A Dm Bb Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, have some cake F C F Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake F Bb We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Garšīgi.</description></item><item><title>Heartbeat</title><link>http://example.org/song/2549-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2549-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat/</guid><description>[Am] I know you told So many times [Am] So many words In different rhymes But [D] i don’t [F] feel the [G] same [Am] I wasn’t innocent, i know [Am] And things i did for sure were wrong The [D] time has [F] passed so [G] long Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me [Am] I’m getting wild when i’m alone [Am] I learned by heart youre not my own But [D] i never [F] asked you to be[G]long [Am] Your my desire and my pain [Am] But all the battles are in vain You [D] mean more [F] than anything to [G] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me [D] You’re the one i need You’re the [F] air that i breath [D] Don’t throw my heart away I want you to [E] stay Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat</description></item><item><title>I Wanna</title><link>http://example.org/song/2548-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_I_Wanna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2548-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_I_Wanna/</guid><description>[Am] I&amp;#39;d like to go away, but [E] it&amp;#39;s easier to say That [A m] you know all the tricks that make... that [E] make me stay [Am] I&amp;#39;m ready to support this [E] artful game you always play &amp;#39;Cause [Am] you don&amp;#39;t know the fee that you will [E] later, later pay [F] Today you think you are the winner, [C] today you think you are the king You [E] make me sweat in my emotions under your flyway, flyway [Am] wing I wanna be the [E] sunshine in your eyes, I wanna be the [Am] light from shooting stars I wanna be [E] queen in your sweetest lies, I wanna be the [Am] love-spark in your eyes I wanna be the [E] sunshine in your eyes, I wanna be the [Am] light from shooting stars I wanna be [E] queen in your sweetest lies I wanna be the love-spark in your [Am] eyes Ay ay ay ay ay ay.</description></item><item><title>Circus In The Sky</title><link>http://example.org/song/2540-Audience_Killers_-_Circus_In_The_Sky/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 12:58:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2540-Audience_Killers_-_Circus_In_The_Sky/</guid><description>[C] All I see is dark and clear [C] All I feel is here and real [Am] And when I’m wide awake [F] [Am] I see all my mistakes [F] [Am] And all the bones I break [F] [Am] The world hears me say [F] My [C] sky, [Am] [F] Circus in [C] my [Am] sky My [C] sky, [Am] [F] Circus in [C] my [Am] sky [C] You and [Am] I The [C] stars in your [Am] eyes Shine [C] bright to [Am] me You’re [C] all i [Am] need [C] This is [F] not the [Am] end [C] We’re [F] on the [Am] edge [Am] Me and [C] You, Well [G] get [F] this [Am] through [Am] On our [C] way, This [G] is [F] our [Am] way [Am] Me and [C] You, Well [G] get [F] this [Am] through [Am] On our [C] way, This [G] is [F] our [Am] way My [C] sky [F][C][Am]</description></item><item><title>I Can</title><link>http://example.org/song/2519-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_I_Can/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 22:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2519-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_I_Can/</guid><description>One more day, one more night Hard to say what’s on my mind I tried, I tried Every thought on my mind Makes me feel that love is blind This time, this time I will follow, follow you I will follow, follow you I can, I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again Then the storms that we survive They let me back to life I tried, you know that I tried Now that you are next to me I can feel infinity again I feel alive I will follow, follow you I will follow, follow you I can, I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again I can, yes I can I can, I can see you again I can, yes I can I can I will follow, follow you I will follow, follow you I can, I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again.</description></item><item><title>Demons</title><link>http://example.org/song/2466-Crow_Mother_-_Demons/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 11:36:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2466-Crow_Mother_-_Demons/</guid><description>Those sleepless nights Too much demons to fight Somebody stop the time Too much people around I&amp;#39;m loosing peace that I found Have to find it again Wake me up Nightmare has gone Wake me up Nightmare has gone I&amp;#39;ts a new day It&amp;#39;s a new life But I’ll never know What tomorrow brings I&amp;#39;ts a new day It&amp;#39;s a new life But I’ll never know What tomorrow brings I hear a laughter of clouds They’re asking me out Teasing my spirit and my belief I’m ready to follow, to go now Wake me up Let me scream I&amp;#39;ts a new day It&amp;#39;s a new life But I’ll never know What tomorrow brings I&amp;#39;ts a new day It&amp;#39;s a new life But I’ll never know What tomorrow brings I&amp;#39;ts a new day It&amp;#39;s a new life But I’ll never know What tomorrow brings I&amp;#39;ts a new day It&amp;#39;s a new life You come and go For a million miles and more Yeah</description></item><item><title>Gray Wolf</title><link>http://example.org/song/2465-Crow_Mother_-_Gray_Wolf/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 Jan 2016 11:36:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2465-Crow_Mother_-_Gray_Wolf/</guid><description>He came to fight hunger World slowly walking Keeping eye on you Bite the tail Overkill... take the lead Run them free And you know Show some teeth Playing hard Hunt till dark Wolves live for today Their kill is fast Keeping eyes on a prey we will follow him at last .....gray wolf Silent screams Painful dreams Bloody ground Demon signs Red skies victim&amp;#39;s march Keep the light in the eye Let&amp;#39;s begin this fight And you know Show some teeth Playing hard Hunt till dark Wolves live for today, Their kill is fast, keeping eyes on a prey, We will follow him at last Wolves live for today, Their kill is fast, keeping eyes on a prey, We will follow him at last .</description></item><item><title>Beauty in the Ordinary</title><link>http://example.org/song/2402-Laura_Lo_-_Beauty_In_The_Ordinary/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2015 18:33:56 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2402-Laura_Lo_-_Beauty_In_The_Ordinary/</guid><description>[C] Chasing cars and [G] racing snails [Am] They [C] like to hang out [G] in the woods [Am] They [C] hate early [G] mornings and [Am] dead, sad faces There’s [C] some kind of [G] sorce[Am]ry But [F] when they start to [Am] daydream their minds [G] float straight to the [C] stars But [F] when they start to [Am] daydream their minds [G] float straight to the [C] stars [C] Look around There’s something [Am] more [F] Can’t you see the [G] beauty in the ordinary [C] Look around There’s something [Am] more [F] Can’t you see the [G] beauty in the ordinary [C] Building up and [G] crashing down [Am] They’re [C] chatting with some [G] ghost [Am] friends Seems [C] like the [G] golden days are [Am] gone forever The [C] world they [G] used to [Am] know But [F] when they start to [Am] daydream their minds [G] float straight to the [C] stars But [F] when they start to [Am] daydream their minds [G] float straight to the [C] stars [C] Look around There’s something [Am] more [F] Can’t you see the [G] beauty in the ordinary [C] Look around There’s something [Am] more [F] Can’t you see the [G] beauty in the ordinary</description></item><item><title>Dangers Of Boredom</title><link>http://example.org/song/2369-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Dangers_Of_Boredom/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2015 18:10:01 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2369-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Dangers_Of_Boredom/</guid><description>Em G Show me the place Em G Give me the reason G I’ll find the way Em But I wont come too close Em G 7 p.m. Em G At your favorite corner G I’ll have a plan Em G And we see where it goes Em Oh, lord G Would you lend me some words C She’s got the melody Am And I’ll bring the thirds Em G All that we want is to sing C Am Love is a meaning of everything Em G Let’s hide on the trains Em G And in the flats of strangers G Dangers of boredom Em Could eat us alive A Lets dive into the sky Em And move all the mountains A Lets share the music G Night and day</description></item><item><title>L.O.V.E.</title><link>http://example.org/song/2301-C-Stones_-_LOVE/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 06:36:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2301-C-Stones_-_LOVE/</guid><description>You! No reason to be blue I know there’s always someone Exchanging looks with you Right! Love is sugary pain But just put up a smile now And let it through your veins Love’s burning bright like sunshine Love’s always in love with you And you, and you, and you [F] L.O.[G] V.E. [C] Don’t forget [Am] about me [F] On this [G] Saturday [C] night [Am] [F] L.O.[G] V.E. [C] I need you [Am] around me [F] On this [G] Saturday [C] night [Am] Feel emotions are released And wherever they’d take us I promise You’ll be pleased Love’s burning bright like sunshine Love’s always in love with you And you, and you, and you [F] L.</description></item><item><title>Don't Dream It's Over</title><link>http://example.org/song/2299-C-Stones_-_Dont_Dream_Its_Over/</link><pubDate>Tue, 04 Aug 2015 06:26:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2299-C-Stones_-_Dont_Dream_Its_Over/</guid><description>[C] There is freedom within, [Am] there is freedom without [F] Try to catch the deluge in a paper [E] cup [C] There&amp;#39;s a battle ahead, [Am] many battles are lost [F] But you&amp;#39;ll never see the end of the road while you&amp;#39;re [E] travelling with me [F] Hey now, [G] hey now Don&amp;#39;t [C] dream it&amp;#39;s [Am] over [F] Hey now, [G] hey now When the [C] world comes [Am] in [F] They come, [G] they come [C] To build a wall [Am] between us [F] We know they won&amp;#39;t win [G] [C] Now I&amp;#39;m towing my car, [Am] there&amp;#39;s a hole in the roof [F] My possessions are causing me suspicion but [E] there&amp;#39;s no proof [C] In the paper today [Am] tales of war and of waste [F] But you turn right over to the [E] T.</description></item><item><title>And You Came</title><link>http://example.org/song/2262-Lauris_Reiniks_-_And_You_Came/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 13:12:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2262-Lauris_Reiniks_-_And_You_Came/</guid><description>[Am] When I open up a [F] page of my past [G] I find it [Am] blue – [Am] Love enough for two [F] but no-one around, [G] Nothing to [Am] do. [Am] I found no [F] no meaning [G] In the world at [E] all [Am] Bravehearted [F] I started [G] Knocking on your [E] wall And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] I will never be the [E] same And you [Am] came Like a flame That I [F] hope will never die [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you came And you [F] got me outta frame [G] I will never be the [E] same [Am] When I open up a [F] page of my past [G] I find it [Am] white [Am] Now it&amp;#39;s getting clear the [F] colours appear [G] Out of your [Am] light [Am] The freedom [F] I cherished [G] Was a fool&amp;#39;s para[E]dise [Am] But when I [F] met you I [G] got huma[E]nized And you [Am] came Like a [F] flame [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] I will never be the [E] same And you [Am] came Like a flame That I [F] hope will never die [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you came And you [F] got me outta frame [G] I will never be the [E] same [Am] My shelter [F] and my shooting [G] star That&amp;#39;s [E] what you are to me [Am] You made my [F] life [G] complete (so [E] complete) [Am] It feels so [F] good The past is [G] gone The [E] past is done [Am] No white, no [F] blue [G] I&amp;#39;ll stay with [E] you (stay with you) And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] I will never be the [E] same And you [Am] came Like a [F] flame [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] I will never be the [E] same And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] I will never be the [E] same And you [Am] came Like a [F] flame [G] Showing me a whole new [C] world And you [Am] came And you [F] came [G] I will never be the [E] same And you [Am] came</description></item><item><title>Life Jacket Under Your Seat</title><link>http://example.org/song/2241-Instrumenti_-_Life_Jacket_Under_Your_Seat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 12:51:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2241-Instrumenti_-_Life_Jacket_Under_Your_Seat/</guid><description>[Dm] &amp;#39;till [G] today [F] you thought you [C] were looking [Dm] for some[G]thing [F] really [C] specific that&amp;#39;s [Dm] a bles[G]sing [F] you&amp;#39;ve come to [C] us - final[F]ly we are [G] here to [F] help you to [C] undergo [Dm] it&amp;#39;s not sim[G]ple [F] finding a [C] painless way [Dm] to stum[G]ble [F] but not to [C] go astray [Dm] any[G]way [F] you will be [C] guided to a [Dm] place that [G] we have [F] kept in [G] secret &amp;#39;till [F] today there must be something more &amp;#39;cause [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat it&amp;#39;s [Dm] not [G] simple [F] finding the [C] only way [Dm] to stum[G]ble but [F] not to [C] go astray [Dm] nice to [G] know [F] that God is [C] with us [Dm] today is the [G] first day [F] of the [G] rest of your [F] life you always know that there&amp;#39;s a [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat [C] life jacket [F] life jacket is [G] under your seat</description></item><item><title>Just For You</title><link>http://example.org/song/2210-Dons_Arturs_Singirejs_-_Just_For_You/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 08:16:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2210-Dons_Arturs_Singirejs_-_Just_For_You/</guid><description>[C] Every day I am watching you [Am] Every night I am dreaming of you [F] Every day, [C] every night - just [G] you [C] Every step, every move [Am] Every breath I am getting from you [F] Every day, [C] every night - just [G] you [Am] I [C] am [F] afraid to [Em] say How much I [Am] love you, ouu [G] Af[F]raid of [G] truth [C] Love can be such a beautiful [Am] Love can be so much wonderful [F] Love can [C] be [F] anything [G] for [F] us [G] [C] Every day I am watching you [Am] Every night I am dreaming of you [F] Every day, [C] every night - just [G] you [C] Every step, every move [Am] Every breath I am getting from you [F] Every day, [C] every night - just [G] you [Am] I [C] am [F] afraid to [Em] say How much I [Am] love you, ouu [G] Af[F]raid of [G] truth [C] Love can be such a beautiful [Am] Love can be so much wonderful [F] Love can [C] be [F] anything [G] anything for [F] us [G] [Am] Show me the [Em] way to your [F] life [Am] Gimme the [Em] key to your [F] soul [Am] All the [Em] time I will [F] fight for [G] you Just for [E] you 3x [G] Love can be such a beautiful [Em] Love can be so much wonderful [C] Love can [G] be [C] Anything (anything) [D] anything (anything) Love for [C] us [D]</description></item><item><title>Dangerous To Me</title><link>http://example.org/song/2182-Ladybird_-_Dangerous_To_Me/</link><pubDate>Sat, 27 Jun 2015 16:32:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2182-Ladybird_-_Dangerous_To_Me/</guid><description>[Am] You and me, we can be The [C] honey and the [G] bee [Am] Come to me, play with me And [C] be my fanta[G]sy In the [F] pouring rain Come [G] on and set me free Cause we [F] are the same To[G]night it&amp;#39;s for [D] real [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] You are dangerous to me [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] Yeah yeah yeah Ooh let me [Am] drown in you, just fall into A [C] deeper shade of [G] blue You make me [Am] feel so good, I knew you would You [C] know just what you&amp;#39;ve got to [G] do Now it [F] feels as if you&amp;#39;re taking [C] over me So [E] can&amp;#39;t you see That you&amp;#39;re [G] dangerous to [D] me [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] You are dangerous to me [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] Yeah yeah yeah In the [F] pouring rain Come [G] on and set me free Cause we [F] are the same To[G]night it&amp;#39;s for [D] real [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] You are dangerous to me [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] Yeah yeah yeah Now it [F] feels as if you&amp;#39;re taking [C] over me So [E] can&amp;#39;t you see That you&amp;#39;re [G] dangerous to [D] me [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] You are dangerous to me [Am] Dam dam dam do di do di dam dam [G] Yeah yeah yeah</description></item><item><title>Beyond The Fence</title><link>http://example.org/song/2181-Audience_Killers_-_Beyond_The_Fence/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2015 06:53:05 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2181-Audience_Killers_-_Beyond_The_Fence/</guid><description>[F] As you see the [C] colors land upon [Am] everything you do, [G] It starts to make sense [F] Simple things [C] like a balloon, if you [Am] let them away, [G] They&amp;#39;ll stay beyond your fence [F] You got [C] carried away from the [Am] streets of people [G] passing by [F] Somewhere far [C] I see the [Am] lights reflecting [G] in the sky [F] My head surround [C] the sounds, I [Am] clearly hear them [G] calling me [F] As you see the [C] colors land upon [Am] everything you do, [G] It starts to make sense [F] Simple things [C] like a balloon, if you [Am] let them away, [G] They&amp;#39;ll stay beyond your fence [F] And I never [C] had a doubt [Am] that I&amp;#39;ll find my way, [G] Looking from the top [F] The world spins [C] around, I&amp;#39;m on a track, [Am] it goes around And I [G] swear to never stop.</description></item><item><title>Love injected</title><link>http://example.org/song/2175-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2175-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected/</guid><description>[Em] You bring [G] the light [C] to my darkest [Am] side, babe [Em] The day, [G] the night [C] split to cure the [Am] sight, ooh [Em] You care, [G] you animate [C] You guard me bare, [Am] bring up the heart rate Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] [Em] Your eye’s a good mirror, [G] look under the cover [C] Love is above [Am] all [Em] I’m safe into your hands [G] Let’s move away, [C] the edges ex[Am]pand Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] Show me the [Em] source of the light, I’m becoming [C] affected Seeing the [Em] glow of the white is what I have de[C]tected Feeling [Em] again I’m alive, it’s your shining re[C]flected Love in[Em]jected, love in[C]jected Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] [Em][G][C][Am] Oh, oh, oh, oh Oh, oh, oh, oh.</description></item><item><title>Footprints and Hearts</title><link>http://example.org/song/2155-Audience_Killers_-_Footprints_And_Hearts/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 07:07:31 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2155-Audience_Killers_-_Footprints_And_Hearts/</guid><description>People come and [C] go, [G] in and [Am] out of your [F] life People come and [C] go, [G] go, go [Am] [F] People come and [C] go, [G] in and [Am] out of your [F] life People come and [C] go, [G] go, go [Am] [F] [C] Few of [G] us stick [Am] around for a [F] lifetime [C] Most are [G] here for [Am] a [F] season [C] Love is [G] love and [Am] never goes [F] away The [C] world’s [G] like that [Am] for no [F] reason People come and [C] go, [G] in and [Am] out of your [F] life People come and [C] go, [G] go, go [Am] [F] People come and [C] go, [G] in and [Am] out of your [F] life People come and [C] go, [G] go, go [Am] [F] [C] Satis[G]fied [Am] with your [F] love I’m [C] satis[G]fied [Am] with your [F] love [C] Satis[G]fied [Am] with your [F] love I’m [C] satis[G]fied [Am] with your [F] love [C] Hellos and [G] goodbyes are [Am] diffi[F]cult [C] What makes [G] someone [Am] stay in our [F] lives [C] Nothing’s [G] the same, [Am] everything’s [F] changing The [C] world’s [G] like that [Am] for no [F] reason People come and [C] go, [G] in and [Am] out of your [F] life People come and [C] go, [G] go, go [Am] [F] People come and [C] go, [G] in and [Am] out of your [F] life People come and [C] go, [G] go, go [Am] [F]</description></item><item><title>Lighthouse</title><link>http://example.org/song/2148-Audience_Killers_-_Lighthouse/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 06:34:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2148-Audience_Killers_-_Lighthouse/</guid><description>And [C] I don&amp;#39;t know if [F] I can do [G] Anything with[C]out you And [C] I don&amp;#39;t know if [F] I can do [G] Anything at [C] all [Am] I got nothing left to [F] do For [C] you, my [G] love And [Am] I got nothing left to [F] say To [C] you, my [G] love And [C] I don&amp;#39;t know if [F] I can do [G] Anything with[C]out you And [C] I don&amp;#39;t know if [F] I can do [G] Anything at [C] all And now we [F] sleep tight on the [G] beachside Pretending [Am] that we&amp;#39;re just fine [C] And now we [F] sleep tight on the [G] beachside Pretending [Am] that we&amp;#39;re just fine [C] [Am] I have bet every[F]thing On our [C] love, I can&amp;#39;t rise [G] above And [Am] now I&amp;#39;m sure that I can&amp;#39;t [F] do Any[C]thing about [G] you And [C] I don&amp;#39;t know if [F] I can do [G] Anything with[C]out you And [C] I don&amp;#39;t know if [F] I can do [G] Anything at [C] all And now we [F] sleep tight on the [G] beachside Pretending [Am] that we&amp;#39;re just fine [C] And now we [F] sleep tight on the [G] beachside Pretending [Am] that we&amp;#39;re just fine [C]</description></item><item><title>Airport</title><link>http://example.org/song/2149-Audience_Killers_-_Airport/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 06:15:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2149-Audience_Killers_-_Airport/</guid><description>[C] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [G] world wide love [Am] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [F] world wide love [C] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [G] world wide love [Am] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [F] world wide love [C] I&amp;#39;m married to the [G] night, I don&amp;#39;t have [Am] to hide [F] [C] Dancing with the [G] moon in the [Am] light of [F] stars [C] Such a [G] strange, [Am] such a [F] strange feeling in my [C] chest Such a [G] strange, [Am] [F] such a strange feeling [C] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [G] world wide love [Am] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [F] world wide love [C] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [G] world wide love [Am] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [F] world wide love [C] Such a [G] strange, [Am] such a [F] strange feeling in my [C] chest Such a [G] strange, [Am] [F] such a strange feeling [C] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [G] world wide love [Am] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [F] world wide love [C] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [G] world wide love [Am] World wide love it&amp;#39;s [F] world wide love</description></item><item><title>Banjo Laura</title><link>http://example.org/song/2131-Lauris_Reiniks_-_Banjo_Laura/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2015 17:38:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2131-Lauris_Reiniks_-_Banjo_Laura/</guid><description>[Am] So she walks in[F]to a bar and talks [C] This and that, nice and slow [G] Here we go…. All [Am] eyes on her- a [F] stranger from the North [C] While she goes back and forth [G] Then she stops and pulls… [Am] Uh, ah, ah, ah, [F] uh, ah, ah, [C] uh. …a magic [G] string. Who is she? [Am] La la-la-la-Laura - she [F] said her name [C] Winked her eye, started [G] out the game [Am] La-la-la-la Laura the [F] banjo girl [C] Who was she?</description></item><item><title>In You</title><link>http://example.org/song/1909-The_Mundane_-_In_You/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 10:58:19 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1909-The_Mundane_-_In_You/</guid><description>Inftro 4x (ceturtajā reizē nespēlē pēdējo noti) E-----7-------7-------8-7------------ B---8---8---8---8---8-----8---8/10--- G-7-------9-------7---------7------9- Am G I am in you Am G now I can be true Am G you cheer up my life Am with every little smile G what comes like a bloom B C Would you be a part of me D G and comprehend my fears within B C would you cease my aching peace D or you will simply leave G Em Today I start my life for good C And hoist the flag in color blue G Em C To be in to be in you Am G Now I can be blind Am G &amp;#39;cause you are my guide Am G there&amp;#39;s nothing more to lose Am there&amp;#39;s something more to chose G in my life</description></item><item><title>Lucky</title><link>http://example.org/song/1834-Tumsa_-_Lucky/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 19:14:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1834-Tumsa_-_Lucky/</guid><description>I have my lucky package of cigarettes in my left hand I have my lucky girl&amp;#39;s hand right in my right hand I have my lucky day I have my lucky face I&amp;#39;m so lucky yeah I have my lucky photo in my lucky passport&amp;#39;s first page I look so damn lucky that others don&amp;#39;t even love me I have my lucky day I have my lucky face I&amp;#39;m so so lucky I&amp;#39;m so so lucky as man can ever be I&amp;#39;m so lucky, lucky I&amp;#39;m so lucky as man can be I&amp;#39;m so lucky, lucky as I&amp;#39;ve ever been before as I&amp;#39;ve ever been before as I&amp;#39;ve ever been before as I&amp;#39;ve ever been before as I&amp;#39;ve ever been before.</description></item><item><title>Born to be drunk</title><link>http://example.org/song/1806-The_Hobos_-_Born_To_Be_Drunk/</link><pubDate>Wed, 10 Sep 2014 18:40:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1806-The_Hobos_-_Born_To_Be_Drunk/</guid><description>and you come then you go but maybe there is something you don&amp;#39;t know and you go then you come but maybe there is something left undone but maybe it&amp;#39;s the wrong number maybe it&amp;#39;s another door i should forget about every thing go out and drink get drunk and sing born to be here born to be drunk like a psychedelic funk... can you give me some now can you give me some and you rise then you fall but maybe there&amp;#39;s something out of control and you fall then you rise but maybe there is something wrong whith your eyes but maybe it&amp;#39;s the wrong number.</description></item><item><title>Hello From Mars</title><link>http://example.org/song/1711-FLY_-_Hello_From_Mars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 04:05:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1711-FLY_-_Hello_From_Mars/</guid><description>Ievads: Dm [C] Time would have passed me by if [Em] I Had never asked you [F] why Your eyes were open [Dm] wide That [G] day you saw me [C] cry [C] I&amp;#39;m not that kind of [Em] girl Who only dreams of [F] pearls Just give me wings of [Dm] love And make it [G] real Cause [Am] I&amp;#39;m not [F] afraid Of a [Dm] blade That we [G] need to cross to[C]day But I&amp;#39;m [F] scared To be [Dm] shared By someone [G] else Cause [C] this is gonna be The [F] day that we will meet When [Dm] heaven comes so [F] down to Earth To [G] say hello from Mars Starpspēle: Am Em F Dm [C] My emotions take me [Em] high They seem to reach the [F] sky I still believe we [Dm] try To [G] hit the ground or [C] fly [Am] Life is a [G] mystery Like a [C] perfect harmo[Dm]ny [C] No one knows that [D] day when love Will [G] come and set you [A] free</description></item><item><title>Lost in Space</title><link>http://example.org/song/1570-The_Hobos_-_Lost_In_Space/</link><pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2013 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1570-The_Hobos_-_Lost_In_Space/</guid><description>The Hobos - Lost in space Welcome to worlwide weblines, please fasten the body scan belt and draw your attention to the hologram map to your right and type your destination, warning, we are not responsible for losing your body information, you may end up forever lost in space, and remember, we can not stop your thinking. Em D C Between the shelters from the delight Em D Em Among the stars and black cold night Em D C You&amp;#39;re trembling and losing your mind G D You&amp;#39;re lost in space G D You&amp;#39;re lost in space Refrain: Em D Em C Hey now you got the last chance Em D C Fade out fade out Em D Em Far out up in the sky C G High high Em D Em You have to stay alive Em G D We want you to come back from high Em D C Back to the same world G D Out of space G .</description></item><item><title>Colder 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/1603-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Colder_2/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2013 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1603-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Colder_2/</guid><description>Bm Em F#m come, oh, come early i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm Em F#m Em Em D A keep the night burning to shine our love always, always Bm pictures on the wall her pictures on my wall A G she’s so beautiful, so beautiful Bm climbing up to fall i’m climbing up to fall A G i’m still staying cool, i’m staying cool Bm G one day i’ll find you just to prove that i’m real A D /D/C# out of love and hate, of love and hate Bm G and losing ties with common sense, baby, i know A F# i will make a bridge to place where my mind goes Bm Em F#m come, oh, come early i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm Em F#m keep the night burning to shine our love always, always Bm thousands of the walls 8 billions of the walls A G she’s so beautiful, so beautiful Bm digi-dogs around her digi-dogs around A G i’m still staying cool, well, i’m staying cool Bm G i’m losing all i have and all i ever will A D /D/C# out of love and hate, of love and hate Bm G i’m losing daydreams and a good night sleep A F# oh, baby, our passions are hiding deep Bm Em F#m come, oh, come early i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm Em F#m keep the night burning to shine our love always, always Solo : Em Em D A Em Em D A</description></item><item><title>Angels in disguise</title><link>http://example.org/song/1339-Musiqq_-_Angels_In_Disguise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1339-Musiqq_-_Angels_In_Disguise/</guid><description>Intro: Am7 | C | G | Dm7 Am7 C G Woke up tonight, looked at the moon, Dm7 Am7 Blinding light filled up my room. C G Looked to my right – my better half, Dm7 Am7 And it’s alright, if it’s all I have, C G I let it ride, I’m satisfied, Just be mine. Chorus: Am Kill me with killa kiss, C Kill me with tempting lips, G Stare at me with candy eyes, Dm7 Love me with luscious thighs.</description></item><item><title>Hard To Be Alone</title><link>http://example.org/song/771-Exprimer_-_Hard_To_Be_Alone/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2008 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/771-Exprimer_-_Hard_To_Be_Alone/</guid><description>C The heart is beautiful Am The heart is just one G It`s the place, F G Where the love is borned C It shines in the sky, Am It shines through the mountains G It`s a wonderful thing F G That has to be watched Piedz. 2x C It`s hard to be alone G It`s hard to be amazed Am F G It`s hard to be without the love C The heart is beautiful Am The heart is just one G It`s the place, F G Where the love is borned C It shines in the sky, Am It shines through the mountains G It`s a wonderful thing F G That has to be watched Piedz.</description></item><item><title>A Frickin' Xmas Song</title><link>http://example.org/song/585-The_Hobos_-_A_Frickin_Xmas_Song/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Mar 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/585-The_Hobos_-_A_Frickin_Xmas_Song/</guid><description>G C D G unforgetable fealing you may find in a freazing day C D G it is not the first offender its not the funny faith Am D call me back again when christmas is over Am D call me back again when christmas is over Am Em it so bidive when your answering mashine can not answer its the funny fellow one of the floating popultaion but the freazing day may refuse you any information so call me back again when christmas is over so call me back again when christmas is over it so bidive when your answering mashine can not answer so call me back again when christmas is over call me back again when christmas is over it so bidive when your answering mashine can not answer kazlens@inbox.</description></item><item><title>Christian, I'm Gonna Be</title><link>http://example.org/song/545-The_Hobos_-_Christian_Im_Gonna_Be/</link><pubDate>Sat, 26 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/545-The_Hobos_-_Christian_Im_Gonna_Be/</guid><description>Em C G D I used to drink coca cola And eat in McDonalds I sipped whiskey On lonely Saturday nights But now i am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to I am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to Well if you want me to I used to go to different gurus Laugh at Jesus Christ And when you came to me that day I thought that all you said was lies But now i am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to I am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to Well if you want me to I used to make a lot of chicks, And watched Hollywood movies roll joints In ancient Indian cities but now i am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to i am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to mmm am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to i am gonna be a christian christian christian if you want me to well if you want me to well if you want me to well if you want me to well if you want me to well if you want me to</description></item><item><title>Fly Away [TAB]</title><link>http://example.org/song/527-Generalplans_-_Fly_Away_TAB/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/527-Generalplans_-_Fly_Away_TAB/</guid><description>Pants/ievads _____________________ G G/F# Em C _____________________ Piedz ________________________ A C G G/F# Em ________________________ Solo Track 1 W Q Q Q E E E E E E E E Q E||---------------------------------------------------------------| B||--15-----15----------------------------------------------------| G||--12b----12b----12--------------------12h------12h--14--14~----| D||-------------------------14--12h--14-------14------------------| A||---------------------------------------------------------------| E||---------------------------------------------------------------| E E E E E E E E E E Q H -----------------------------------------------------------------| -----------------------------------------------------------------| -----------------------------12h------12h--14--14b----14~--------| -----------12h------12h--14-------14-----------------------------| --12h--14-------14-----------------------------------------------| -----------------------------------------------------------------| Q E E E Q E E E E E E Q E -------------------------------------------------------------| -------------------------------------------------------------| ----------------12----------------12------12--14~--14~-------| --14~-------14------14~-------14------14---------------------| -------------------------------------------------------------| -------------------------------------------------------------| E E E Q E Q Q E E Q Q -----------------------------------------------------------|-----|| -------17--------------------------------------------------|-----|| --16------16--14----12h--------12h--------12h-------------|-----|| --------------------------14-----------14-------14---------|-----|| -----------------------------------------------------------|-----|| -----------------------------------------------------------|-----|| Duration Legend --------------- W - whole H - half Q - quarter E - 8th S - 16th T - 32nd X - 64th .</description></item><item><title>A Day Before Tomorrow</title><link>http://example.org/song/516-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_A_Day_Before_Tomorrow/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/516-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_A_Day_Before_Tomorrow/</guid><description>6|5--3--1--0| Am, G, Dm, E Am me, i&amp;#39;m singing G me, i&amp;#39;m riding Dm E to the place where dreams are hiding Am G kids are kidding, mothers forbiding Dm E songs - under my wing C angels lighting G demons fighting Dm E gold and silver - blinding, blinding C stop or go G say &amp;#39;yes&amp;#39; or &amp;#39;no&amp;#39; Dm E its&amp;#39;a day before tomorrow Dm Am Aha...the world is small and we are one.</description></item><item><title>Among The Suns</title><link>http://example.org/song/517-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Among_The_Suns/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/517-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Among_The_Suns/</guid><description> C G I may seem wise I may seem old F Em Am F G Feels like I just came into this world C G I beg and lie and then regret, F Em Am F G I run and grab and soon forget Dm C I can see I feel two skies above Dm C One to be with, one - to love Em Am I envy them. They never lose, Em Am &amp;#39;cos they have a choice not to choose Dm G I can see I feel two skies above Dm C Clouds and clouds and clouds are passing by Dm C Watch the clouds, while they cross the sky Em Am If I should choose among them all Em Am I&amp;#39;d be confused, I&amp;#39;d feel small Dm G Clouds and clouds and clouds are passing by C G I may seem wise I may seem old F Em Am F G Feels like I just came into this world C G I beg and lie and then regret, F Em Am F G I run and grab and soon forget C G I may seem wise I may seem old F Em Am F G Feels like I just came into this world C G I beg and lie and then regret, F Em Am F G I run and grab and soon forget La la la la la la la la la la Am F G and soon forget La la la la la la la la la la (x10)</description></item><item><title>Billions Of Stars</title><link>http://example.org/song/518-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Billions_Of_Stars/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/518-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Billions_Of_Stars/</guid><description>Intro: Asus4 A x2 D Bm Billions of stars are falling down F#m without touching the ground G D We shine thru the night And when you fade away with a smile my existance is not worth while alone in the sky F#m Bm G Just a little more, and I&amp;#39;ll know beyond the known F#m Bm A Just a little more, no, no, let me go One morning we&amp;#39;ll find out - this is ours, spring and late winter hours and high windy sky The end of the world will arrive silently, will lull us to sleep, will set us free together we&amp;#39;ll die Just a little more, and I&amp;#39;ll know beyond the known Just a little more, no, no, let me go We?</description></item><item><title>Leaving To La</title><link>http://example.org/song/519-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Leaving_To_La/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/519-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Leaving_To_La/</guid><description>Intro: e|--------2--------2---------2---------2-----| B|-----3--------3---------3---------3--------| G|--2--------2---------2---------2-----------| D|-------------------------------------------| A|-------------------------------------------| E|-------------------------------------------| Piano, arranged for guitar (played after intro): e|--10--9---------10--9---------10--9-------------------------| B|----------7-------------5-------------7-------7--8--10------| G|------------------------------------------------------------| D|------------------------------------------------------------| A|------------------------------------------------------------| E|------------------------------------------------------------| Verse: D Hm Nothing comes by accident D Hm Even when you&amp;#39;re dreaming G A If we can&amp;#39;t find a common way G Well, if we can&amp;#39;t find F#m D I&amp;#39;m leavin&amp;#39; to L.A. Or to Tokyo No place is then too far And no place can be too hard I&amp;#39;m leavin&amp;#39; I&amp;#39;m leavin&amp;#39; to L.</description></item><item><title>Beautiful Morning</title><link>http://example.org/song/431-Enas_-_Beautiful_Morning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 12 Nov 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/431-Enas_-_Beautiful_Morning/</guid><description>Intro: D Verse 1 D Bm dream is almost gone .. but I’m still dreamy D Bm what a beautiful life .. when you are sleepi’n D Bm it’s nearly 09.00 AM .. sombody screamin’ D Bm streets already full .. such a wonderful morning Chorus G Bm what a beautiful morning .. funny faces all around G D what a beautiful morning .. please smile for awhile G Bm what a beautiful morning .</description></item><item><title>Lights out</title><link>http://example.org/song/402-Dons_Arturs_Singirejs_-_Lights_Out/</link><pubDate>Fri, 22 Jun 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/402-Dons_Arturs_Singirejs_-_Lights_Out/</guid><description>D Deep inside I know these million miles of road Bm are like our crashing zone G In the headlight, I roll you over D Maybe it&amp;#39;s okay, to try another day Bm when there&amp;#39;s nothing left to say G Away from you has become what&amp;#39;s normal. Em A You act like you don&amp;#39;t care G F# You say it&amp;#39;s always been out me G and my priorities D A Lights out on never never Bm G Lights out on our forever D A G You will be my broken dream The fire lost its flame, but no one is to blame for bailing out on pain I&amp;#39;m heading in a new direction The walls must all come down So I send them to the ground and leave without a sound Away from you has become what&amp;#39;s normal</description></item><item><title>Clown</title><link>http://example.org/song/377-Full_House_-_Clown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Apr 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/377-Full_House_-_Clown/</guid><description>E B Once long time ago A I knew some girl A She fool&amp;#39;d me so E She take my hand B She show me way A She told sweet words A And not that all Some day latter Meet her on the street Don&amp;#39;t wanna see her But she did She came to me and said so She came to me and said: C#m F#m &amp;#34;Uh, boy, I miss You so A Am You are my dream You are my love C#m F#m You&amp;#39;re so cute and you&amp;#39;re so nice A Am Can&amp;#39;t You see you&amp;#39;re my pardise&amp;#34; E B A I dont wanna be your fool B For one night E B A And I don&amp;#39;t wanna be your clown Week latter - Same place She said: &amp;#34;Boy I miss your face&amp;#34; Sweet words And not that all I begin to trust her There was hot night We&amp;#39;re kissin&amp;#39; high And do the things What we never did</description></item><item><title>Green</title><link>http://example.org/song/376-Full_House_-_Green/</link><pubDate>Thu, 12 Apr 2007 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/376-Full_House_-_Green/</guid><description>Intro: Em | C | G | D | e|------------------------------------------ B|------------------------------------------ G|------------------------------------------ D|-----5-4-5-4-5-4-0-5-5-4-5-4-5-4-0-2~----- x 2 A|------------------------------------------ E|------------------------------------------ Em Green green days and green green nights C Green heaven and green green hell Em Green thousands and green green millions C Green you and green green me Em It&amp;#39;s green C It&amp;#39;s all in the green Em All in the green C It&amp;#39;s all in the green All in the green Em C Green green days and green green grass G D Green eyes and green green face Em Everything is green C Everything is green G D Green - if you know what I mean Green green days and green green grass Green eyes and green green face Green light and green green darkness Green you and green green me It&amp;#39;s green It&amp;#39;s all in the green All in the green It&amp;#39;s all in the green All in the green Than one day you came to me and said Yes i will be yours if you will be green Than i take off all my clothes an said Just look at me i&amp;#39;m green i always been green And now when you need i&amp;#39;m all in green I&amp;#39;m all in GREEN</description></item><item><title>Again</title><link>http://example.org/song/321-Full_House_-_Again/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/321-Full_House_-_Again/</guid><description>Intro Am F I wake up in morning - again Radio play old song - again TV show was payti - again Today i will die - again Interlude Am E Dm Am x2 Verse 1 (played with acoustic guit + distortion guit plays chords once) Am E Dm Am e|--------------------- B|--------------------- G|----------7~~~------- D|--7~~~2~~~7~~~7~~~--- A|--7~~~2~~~5~~~7~~~--- E|--5~~~0~~~----5~~~--- Am E Always you can come to me Dm Am Always you can ask me help Am E But today better turn around Dm Am And go away Interlude Am E Dm Am x2 Chorus (with distortion) C F Am G e|--------------------------- B|--------------------------- G|--5555----2222------------- D|--5555333322225555--------- x6 A|--3333333300005555--------- E|------1111----3333--------- C F Always my eyes are opened Am G Always i keep smilin&amp;#39; C F Always you can come to me Am G Always just another day Verse 2 Am E Today my eyes make tears Dm Am Don&amp;#39;t come dry my tears Am E Today i will stand alone Dm Am Sorry but that is life Interlude - Am E Dm Am x2 Chorus Verse 3 Am E Always you can come to me Dm Am Always you can ask me help Am E But today better turn around Dm Am And go away Interlude Am E Dm Am x2 Chorus Intro Chords for acoustic guitar: Am E Dm C F G e|--0--0--1--0--1--3--- B|--1--0--3--1--1--0--- G|--2--1--2--0--2--0--- D|--2--2--0--2--3--0--- A|--0--2--0--3--3--2--- E|--0--0--x--x--1--3--- Something or what?</description></item><item><title>Lonely Feeling</title><link>http://example.org/song/334-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Lonely_Feeling/</link><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/334-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Lonely_Feeling/</guid><description>LONELY FEELING (TO BE LONELY) (Rudens; Veter) INTRO ||Em | A | Em | A || 2x || Em A | Bm | Em A | Bm || 2x PANTS || Em A | Bm | G |A || Em A Bm like ships without anchors G A wide is the ocean, no islands, no shores Em A Bm all is well, only G A this is such a lonely feeling to be lonely fame is illusion bright are the lights and you - you are left in confusion all is well, only this is such a lonely feeling this is such a lonely feeling PIEDZ || Em A | BmSUS4 | Em A | BmSUS4 || || Em A | BmSUS4 | Em A | G | A | G | A | A || Em A BmSUS4 driving fast as fast as i can Em A BmSUS4 or sitting quietly on the windowsill Em A BmSUS4 you&amp;#39;ve got all and nothing Em A Bm just put no more loneliness on my bill Em A G this is such a lonely feeling PANTS || Em A | Bm | G |A || all songs should be happy actors young and soap operas crappy movies are x-rays our destinies are chosing our ways and what should we do?</description></item><item><title>Colder</title><link>http://example.org/song/315-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Colder/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Mar 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/315-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_Colder/</guid><description>Bm G come, oh, come early A D i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm G keep the night burning A F# to shine our love always, always Bm Bm A A Bm pictures on the wall Bm her pictures on my wall A A she’s so beautiful, so beautiful Bm climbing up to fall Bm i’m climbing up to fall A A i’m still staying cool, i’m staying cool Bm Bm one day i’ll find you just to prove that i’m real G F# out of love and hate, of love and hate Bm Bm and losing ties with common sense, baby, i know G F# i will make a bridge to place where my mind goes Bm G come, oh, come early A D i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm G keep the night burning A F# to shine our love always, always Bm thousands of the walls Bm 8 billions of the walls A A she’s so beautiful, so beautiful Bm digi-dogs around Bm her digi-dogs around A A i’m still staying cool, well, i’m staying cool Bm Bm i’m losing all i have and all i ever will G F# out of love and hate, of love and hate Bm Bm i’m losing daydreams and a good night sleep G F# oh, baby, our passions are hiding deep Bm G come, oh, come early A D i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm G keep the night burning A F# to shine our love always, always Bm G come, oh, come early A D i’m afraid of getting colder, colder Bm G keep the night burning A F# to shine our love always, always always, always</description></item><item><title>Bailes par ziņģi</title><link>http://example.org/song/88-Livi_-_Bailes_Par_Zingi/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/88-Livi_-_Bailes_Par_Zingi/</guid><description>G Man bail, ka viss bruģis Em ka viss bruģis ziedošais C D Ar asfalta sūnu apaugs Man bail, ka iz sirdīm ka iz sirdīm sārti košajām Nātres it visas izraus. Piedz. G Em Ai dieva dotajiem,Ai dieva dotajiem, C D Ai dieva dotajiem,viss ir velna dots. Man bail, ka iz sirdīm ka iz sirdīm sārti košajām Nātres it visas izraus. Un kur tad tu muksi Kur tu muksi ,ziņģīt manu Pilsētas meiča ašā Piedz.</description></item><item><title>Dziesma par Sievieti Vāvu no Ruandas</title><link>http://example.org/song/109-SILS_-_Dziesma_Par_Sievieti_Vavu_No_Ruandas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/109-SILS_-_Dziesma_Par_Sievieti_Vavu_No_Ruandas/</guid><description>Bm G Bm A Es cenšos apmelot tos vārdus, ko saki tu man kaut tu jau stāvi tik tālu no manis un es vairs neatpazīstu, jā, tikai vairs caur… tomēr vairs neatpazīstu, bet tu pastāsti man ko es pazaudēju un es tev pateikšu kad Tu pastāsti man ko es pazaudēju… Un es muguru tev vairs nepagriezīšu un savus murgus tev neatdošu un nepārlēkšu šim vakaram, kaut arī mans rīts kā tāds bende gaida, kad es atvēršu acis, lai nocirstu man galvu… Em Bm C D Slāpst?</description></item><item><title>If You're Gonna Be a Hero</title><link>http://example.org/song/55-Jauns_Meness_-_If_Youre_Gonna_Be_A_Hero/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/55-Jauns_Meness_-_If_Youre_Gonna_Be_A_Hero/</guid><description>Intro: | G D Em | C D | 4x G D Em If you&amp;#39;re gonna be a hero C D Try to travel in time G D Em When the clock will hit zero C D Blow thw candle out G D Em Raise Your arms and start to travel C D Leave Your things at home G D Em A hundred years You will unravel C D Don&amp;#39;t stand in one place G D Em You can toss stones into the sea C Telling no one your name G D Em Anyone can still wish to be C A hero in their dreams.</description></item><item><title>It Is Easy</title><link>http://example.org/song/6-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_It_Is_Easy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Feb 2007 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/6-Prata_Vetra-Brainstorm_-_It_Is_Easy/</guid><description>Em Bm Just like the sun D A I tried to touch but it`s freezing Em Bm You are my gun D A You know, you can choot me, it`s easy A Em Yeah...Hey... D Bm You wanted a star and i say it is easy Yeah... Just like the flame But my fingers and hands are freezing You`re not the same I can feel it, you know, it`s so easy Yeah.</description></item></channel></rss>