<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Linda Leen on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/linda-leen/</link><description>Recent content in Linda Leen on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:08:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/linda-leen/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dziesma par lāčiem</title><link>http://example.org/song/3996-Linda_Leen_-_Dziesma_Par_Laciem/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:08:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3996-Linda_Leen_-_Dziesma_Par_Laciem/</guid><description>Am B Ziemeļos vēji asi, E Am Asaras acīs rieš. Dm Čīkstošo zemes asi, E Lāči rāmi griež. Dm Gadsimti garām paslīd, C Am Jūra zem lediem trīc. E Lāči griež polu asi, Am Zemei griežas līdz . Am Dm Lāā la la la lā la lāā E Am Riti zeme neapstāj. Lāčiem ir rūpe viena, Zemei lai ritums raits. Vīriem lai kādā dienā , Acīs atplaukst smaids. Gadu vai divus ātrāk, Roka lai roku skar.</description></item><item><title>I Wish I Knew</title><link>http://example.org/song/3106-Linda_Leen_-_I_Wish_I_Knew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:49:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3106-Linda_Leen_-_I_Wish_I_Knew/</guid><description>Everytime you’re walking by I feel like flying high But then I realize: The blue is in your eyes Telling you how much I care makes you stop, sit and stare So then I walk away and you don’t make me stay Your hesitation seems too long So in all confusion I wrote you this song I wish I knew what should I do To make the sun shine, to make you all mine Here is my heart, don’t break it apart Look in my eyes and read: It’s you that I need My mind says stop to dream and row another stream And walk another land and try to understand My heart beats only for you, and yours?</description></item><item><title>Let's Go Insane</title><link>http://example.org/song/3105-Linda_Leen_-_Lets_Go_Insane/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 09:49:28 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3105-Linda_Leen_-_Lets_Go_Insane/</guid><description>There’s a place I used to know It was all so beautiful It was only for me and you Would you come into my place? Would you go into my shoes? Would you stand the hard embrace? When I give my heart When I fall in love It will be the same Baby, baby, I wanna be your star Let me hide and fall in your sky Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby, let’s go insane Lay your body next to mine Feel the ground and heaven above Hear the sound of my soul I don’t wanna fight no more I don’t want you to lie Don’t want me to cry, don’t wanna hide When I give my heart When I fall in love It will be the same Baby, baby, I wanna be your star Let me hide and fall in your sky Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby It is true Love you Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby Let’s go insane Baby, baby, I wanna be your star Let me hide and fall in your sky Don’t wanna hurt you, it is true I just wanna love you Come in to my life and, baby, let’s go insane</description></item><item><title>I Was a Lonely Girl</title><link>http://example.org/song/3098-Linda_Leen_-_I_Was_A_Lonely_Girl/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 09:37:32 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3098-Linda_Leen_-_I_Was_A_Lonely_Girl/</guid><description>I was a girl with an empty space in my heart I was a rock that stands on the empty beach, oh my God I had no home, had no money, had no place to go But, baby, you moved me on I didn&amp;#39;t cry, I didn&amp;#39;t laugh I had two eyes, but I was blind I had no grief, no happiness There was no order neither mess I was always in between humbleness and self-esteem You made me live I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo If you have lived, You don&amp;#39;t want just to exist anymore Here is my heart, boy I know you&amp;#39;ll keep it in warmth You have made me love, Made me hate, too I am thankful to you and, Baby, you moved me I didn&amp;#39;t cry, I didn&amp;#39;t laugh I had two eyes, but I was blind I had no grief, no happiness There was no order neither mess I was always in between humbleness and self-esteem You made me live I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo I was a lonely girl till I met my man Who will love me completely And will understand me I was a lonely girl, But I found love so true You enchanter, oh you- See what you do with your voodoo</description></item><item><title>Beyond Velvet Skin</title><link>http://example.org/song/2872-Linda_Leen_-_Beyond_Velvet_Skin/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 13:20:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2872-Linda_Leen_-_Beyond_Velvet_Skin/</guid><description>Can you see behind the velvet soft skin, hotblooded flesh? what do you feel is beyond ? dig deeper than just hot breath, blood enriched with raw energy fruity taste of my body it’s in the air, yeah will you ever be close enough to see me clearly through your misty eyes but you don’t care, yeah you just go for hot breath, blood enriched with raw energy fruity taste of my body it’s in the air but sin is so tempting</description></item><item><title>Dziesmiņa par lāčiem (Песня про медведей)</title><link>http://example.org/song/2510-Linda_Leen_-_Dziesmina_Par_Laciem/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2016 11:45:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2510-Linda_Leen_-_Dziesmina_Par_Laciem/</guid><description>[Am] Ziemeļos vēji [Dm] asi, [E] Asaras acīs [Am] rieš. [Am] Čīkstošo zemes [Dm] asi, [G] Lāči rāmi [C] griež. [Dm] Gadsimti garām [G] paslīd, [C] Jūra zem lediem [Am] trīc. [Am] Lāči griež polu [Dm] asi, [E] Zemei griežas [Am] līdz. [A7] Lāā la la la [Dm] lā la lāā [E] Rīti zeme [Am] neapstāj. [A7][Dm] [E][Am] [Am] Lāčiem ir rūpe [Dm] viena, [E] Zemei lai ritums [Am] raits. [Am] Vīriem lai kādā [Dm] dienā, [G] Acīs atplaukst [C] smaids.</description></item></channel></rss>