<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>supernova 2019 on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/tags/supernova-2019/</link><description>Recent content in supernova 2019 on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:41:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/supernova-2019/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cherry Absinthe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3469-Edgars_Kreilis_McKreilis_-_Cherry_Absinthe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3469-Edgars_Kreilis_McKreilis_-_Cherry_Absinthe/</guid><description>I don’t remember A lot of things But the one thing I remember Is the last night of December I didn’t notice You were around How can I be so lifted At the same time feel so twisted? Oooh! I’m not fluent But the language of our love Takes me higher and above Oooh! How do you do it? ‘Cos the language of our love Takes me higher and above Oooh!</description></item><item><title>Cutting the Wire</title><link>http://example.org/song/3466-Samanta_Tina_-_Cutting_The_Wire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3466-Samanta_Tina_-_Cutting_The_Wire/</guid><description>Oooo! Oooo! O! O! Oooo! Oooo! O! O! Oooo! Oooo! O! O! What if I Did not pick up High and dry With no heads up Baby Tell me there&amp;#39;s another way to see this You played me Once what a huge mistake But now it&amp;#39;s twice Don&amp;#39;t give a f*ck I won&amp;#39;t call you Sooo don&amp;#39;t pick up the phone Noooo explaining Noooo excuses I won&amp;#39;t call you Sooo don&amp;#39;t pick up the phone Oooo!</description></item><item><title>Būšu tepat</title><link>http://example.org/song/3468-Liga_Ridere_-_Busu_Tepat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:18:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3468-Liga_Ridere_-_Busu_Tepat/</guid><description>Vai Tava sirds stostās neziņā Beidzot sāku Tevi saprast Tas ir veids, kā Tu tiec cauri tumšai ielai Skrienot ātri, neatskatoties Bet es netieku tev līdz Ja Tev ko vajadzēs, būšu tepat Te vienmēr gaidīšu, būšu tepat Pat ģimenē, Tu vienmēr biji viens Vienatnē mācījies, kas dzīve tāda ir Cīnījies par sevi pats, tā drošu vietu rast Lūk, kādēļ Tu tā skrien – neatskatoties Bet es netieku tev līdz Ja Tev ko vajadzēs, būšu tepat Tevi vienmēr gaidīšu, būšu tepat Kaut mani atstāji – te vienu tālumā Es sekošu Tev ar domām Lai kāds Tevi pasargā Tagad skatos acīs Tev Es redzu, ko meklēji Tu Mīlestība, patiesi, spēj Dziedēt vientulību Šķiet, Tu sāc soļot Jo jūtu Tevi nākam Šis būs jauns sākums Ko sirds Tev rod neziņā Ja Tev ko vajadzēs, būšu tepat Tevi vienmēr gaidīšu, būšu tepat Kaut mani atstāji – te vienu tālumā Es sekošu Tev ar domām Lai kāds Tevi pasargā Lai kāds Tevi pasargā</description></item><item><title>Awe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3463-Laime_Pilniga_-_Awe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3463-Laime_Pilniga_-_Awe/</guid><description>I remember when The dream was over I felt kinda sad And now I feel so odd I need to get there back now Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, lookin’ for place to hide from you I went to my childhood place Climbed in my favourite tree in black and white Saw my beloved ones watchin’ Jim and Kurt Playin’ badminton and both them won I felt uplifted and so I flew Over the hills and the morning dew I felt so alive long ago Don’t know where I’m going but I have to go Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, looking for place to hide from you Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, looking for place to hide from you Ah, I got a secret Ah, I got a secret to hold Ooh, ooh Ooh, ooh, I got a secret I got a secret to hold</description></item><item><title>Fire</title><link>http://example.org/song/3447-Double_Faced_Eels_-_Fire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3447-Double_Faced_Eels_-_Fire/</guid><description>I’ve got a fire burning deep inside Illuminates my way when there’s no light Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire Never was the type to fit in / Least likely to succeed Never was the type to listen / Always marching to my own beat Never had a doubt in my mind / Ain’t got no quit in me All I’ve got’s a burning hunger / cuts and bruises to remind me Learned from my pain and heartache / turned all that into fuel All of the rage that I felt / yeah, I put in my rear-view Feel tall like the highest tower / there ain’t no stopping me All I’ve got’s a burning hunger / and voices in my head, they’re singing I’ve got a fire burning deep inside Illuminates my way when there’s no light Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire Stood on the edge of darkness / Felt my spirit breaking Thought that there&amp;#39;s no going back / My girl, my friends and family saved me Don&amp;#39;t know if I picked the right path / Or where it&amp;#39;s leading me All I&amp;#39;ve got&amp;#39;s a burning hunger / and voices in my head, they&amp;#39;re singing Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire I’ve got a fire, burning deep inside, a fire burning deep inside I’ve got a fire, burning deep inside, a fire burning deep inside I’ve got a fire</description></item><item><title>Listen to the way that I breathe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3445-Laika_Upe_-_Listen_To_The_Way_That_I_Breathe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3445-Laika_Upe_-_Listen_To_The_Way_That_I_Breathe/</guid><description>You keep lying Eyes glued to the ceiling I keep scratching Until you come falling down from the plaster What a disaster, your stare is red Your hands are sewn to the bed The liquids that we used Are floating safe in a drain Now flush them from your brain Listen to the way that I breathe My heartbeat, the way I speak Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Listen to the way that I breathe My heartbeat, the way I speak Face the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Are you back Or just planning to attack The words you speak are sweet But somehow I see through you The demons still hold true!</description></item><item><title>Fireworks</title><link>http://example.org/song/3443-Alekss_Silvers___-_Fireworks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3443-Alekss_Silvers___-_Fireworks/</guid><description>Lying in my bed of silence Know you’re gonna come tonight Thinking of the consequences Asking why Wonder if I think about you Want to know if I still care You’re the one who wants it over But we’re here This love’s incomplete It never will be But it hurts me to breathe All I care for Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn Look into my eyes and tell me Who you really wanna be Enemies, friends or lovers Who are we Said you’re staying with another But you’re always coming back Tired of being undercover Losing track This love’s incomplete It never will be But it helps me to breathe All I care for Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn This isn’t right (This isn’t right) But you’re safe for tonight (Safe for tonight) Out of sight (Out of sight) Holding me tight (Holding me tight) Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn</description></item></channel></rss>