<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Marija Naumova (Marie N) on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/marija-naumova-marie-n/</link><description>Recent content in Marija Naumova (Marie N) on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 18:17:24 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/marija-naumova-marie-n/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Gavilējiet, zvaigznes</title><link>http://example.org/song/3732-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Gavilejiet_Zvaigznes/</link><pubDate>Tue, 26 May 2020 18:17:24 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3732-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Gavilejiet_Zvaigznes/</guid><description>1. Šonakt klusi, klusi debess atver vārtus, lai pa lielo Piena ceļu atnāk kāda spoža zvaigzne, spožākā no visām, lai pār zemi atkal būtu gaisma. Gavilējiet, zvaigznes, gavilējiet gani, dzimis pestītājs, dzimis pestītājs! 2. Šonakt klusi, klusi sevī atver vārtus, ļauj lai lielā prieka vēsts tur ienāk, lai kā spoža zvaigzne atmirdz, kad ir skumji un lai vienmēr sirdī prieku ienes. Gavilējiet, zvaigznes, gavilējiet gani, dzimis pestītājs! Gavilējiet, zvaigznes, gavilējiet gani, dzimis pestītājs, dzimis pestītājs!</description></item><item><title>Hey, Boy, Follow Me</title><link>http://example.org/song/3311-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Hey_Boy_Follow_Me/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 18:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3311-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Hey_Boy_Follow_Me/</guid><description>There are so many places, so many things to see So many different faces, but, baby, look at me I know the scenic mountain where you would go uphill So I know we start dreaming of some vicious devil feel But if you let me lead you because you want to know Don’t hesitate, my darling, just take my hand and go Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide ‘Cause when we walk across my world you’ll be my guiding light You have to hear my ocean, to see my land is wide To feel my deep devotion, experience my light But if you think a stranger is better guiding you I’ll try to understand that if I’m a stranger, too But if you let me lead you because you want to know Don’t hesitate, my darling, just take my hand and go Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide ‘Cause when we walk across my world you’ll be my guiding light Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide ‘Cause when we walk across my world you’ll be my guiding light Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide So, baby, follow-up all on me to be my guiding light</description></item><item><title>For You My Friends</title><link>http://example.org/song/3103-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_For_You_My_Friends/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:19:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3103-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_For_You_My_Friends/</guid><description>One day you’ll understand that you are alone And the world around you, cold and firm like stone And that’s the miracle, you’ll need a real friend To whom you do not have to lie and to pretend And that’s the miracle, you’ll need a real friend To whom you do not have to lie and to pretend You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You’ll see all people in another way In your life, it won’t be a hard and heavy day And that’s the important day, you’ll need a real friend The tell that you are tired, to lie and to pretend And that’s the important day, you’ll need a real friend The tell that you’re tired, to lie and to pretend You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile You have to stop for a moment You have to wait for a while Remember all the friends you’ve needed To say to them thanks and then to smile</description></item><item><title>Kādā jaukā dienā</title><link>http://example.org/song/2628-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Kada_Jauka_Diena/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 13:19:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2628-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Kada_Jauka_Diena/</guid><description>[C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] saule spīd [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] zaļā pļavā [F] rasa krīt [Dm] Kādā jaukā dienā palie[G]kam mēs divatā [Dm] Un pa saules taku tu pie [F] manis ciemos [G] nāc [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] teic labrīt [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] it nekā var [F] neda[G]rīt [Dm] Kādā jaukā dienā ize[G]jam mēs divatā [F] arvien Starp [G] ziediem roku [C] rokā [F] Šajā [C] dienā [F] esam kopā [C] abi mēs [F] Šājā [C] dienā [F][G] [F] Šajā [C] dienā [F] esam laimes [C] šūpolēs [F] Šajā [C] dienā [F] Gribas aizsap[G]ņot pat aiz māko[F]ņiem [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] ceļš tik balts [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] lauka puķes [F] neno[G]vīst [Dm] Kādā jaukā dienā pēkšņi [G] paliek priecīgs prāts [Dm] Jo pa saules taku tu pie [F] manis atkal [G] nāc [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] lietus līst [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] zeme lietu [F] neie[G]nīst [Dm] Šajā jaukā dienā bra[G]dājam mēs divatā [F] arvien Pa [G] peļķēm roku [C] rokā [F] Šajā [C] dienā [F] esam kopā [C] abi mēs [F] Šājā [C] dienā [F][G] [F] Šajā [C] dienā [F] esam laimes [C] šūpolēs [F] Šajā [C] dienā [F] Gribas aizsap[G]ņot pat aiz māko[F]ņiem [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] saule spīd [G] [C] Kādā jaukā dienā [Am] saule spīd, vai [F] lietus [G] līst [Dm] Tik un tā ar tevi palik[G]sim mēs divatā [Dm] Jo pa saules taku tu pie [F] manis atkal [G] nāc [F] Šajās [C] dienās [F] esam kopā [C] abi mēs [F] Laimes [C] mirkļos [F][G] [F] Šajās [C] dienās [F] esam laimes [C] šūpolēs [F] Laimes [C] mirkļus [F] Gribas neaiz[G]mirst, gribas notu[F]rēt [G] [F] Šajās [C] dienās [F] esam kopā [C] abi mēs [F] Laimes [C] mirkļos [F][G] [F] Šajās [C] dienās [F] esam laimes [C] šūpolēs [F] Laimes [C] mirkļus [F] Gribas neaiz[G]mirst, gribas notu[F]rēt [G]</description></item><item><title>Ieskaties acīs</title><link>http://example.org/song/2630-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Ieskaties_Acis/</link><pubDate>Sat, 09 Apr 2016 12:46:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2630-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Ieskaties_Acis/</guid><description>[C] Ieskaties [Em] acīs, [F] lai [G] redzētu [C] tu [C] Kas es tev [Em] esmu [F] un [G] kas esi [C] tu [F] Ieskaties [G] ciešāk, vien [E] ielūko[Am]jies [F] Kā gan tu [C] mani sev [F] iz[G]tēlo[C]jies [C] Neklausies [Em] vārdos [F] un [G] nesaki [C] tos [C] Vārdi bez [Em] jēgas [F] maz [G] prieka mums [C] dos [F] Saki bez [G] vārdiem, lai [E] nepārpro[Am]tu [F] Tu mana [C] mīļā un [F] mans [G] esi [C] tu [C] Aiziesiem [Em] kopā, kur [F] taureņi [G] zied [C] Aiziesim [Em] kopā, kur [F] vēji vien [G] dzied [Dm] Lidosim [Am] pāri, kur [F] negaida [G] mūs [C] Elposim [Em] dziļi un [F] la[G]bi vien [C] būs [C] Pār svešām [Em] jūrām, [F] lai [G] neilgo[C]jos [C] Pār svešām [Em] lūpām, [F] lai [G] nenobī[C]stos [F] No svešām [G] acīm, lai [E] paslēpja[Am]mies [F] Uz savām [C] mājām, reiz [F] at[G]grieža[C]mies [C] Esi kā [Em] puķe, [F] ko [G] pļava man [C] nes [C] Tver manu [Em] elpu, [F] lai [G] vējš neaiz[C]nes [F] Izgaismo [G] telpu, lai [E] gaišs top it [Am] viss [F] Kas manā [C] sirdī, [F] sen [G] kvēlo[C]jis [C] Ieskaties [Em] acīs, [F] lai [G] redzētu [C] tu [C] Kas es tev [Em] esmu [F] un [G] kas esi [C] tu [F] Neklausies [G] vārdos ko [E] tie teiks par [Am] mums [F] Ieskaties [C] sirdī un [F] at[G]bilde [C] būs [C] Aiziesiem [Em] kopā, kur [F] taureņi [G] zied [C] Aiziesim [Em] kopā, kur [F] vēji vien [G] dzied [Dm] Lidosim [Am] pāri, kur [F] negaida [G] mūs [C] Elposim [Em] dziļi un [F] la[G]bi vien [C] būs</description></item><item><title>I Wanna</title><link>http://example.org/song/2548-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_I_Wanna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2548-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_I_Wanna/</guid><description>[Am] I&amp;#39;d like to go away, but [E] it&amp;#39;s easier to say That [A m] you know all the tricks that make... that [E] make me stay [Am] I&amp;#39;m ready to support this [E] artful game you always play &amp;#39;Cause [Am] you don&amp;#39;t know the fee that you will [E] later, later pay [F] Today you think you are the winner, [C] today you think you are the king You [E] make me sweat in my emotions under your flyway, flyway [Am] wing I wanna be the [E] sunshine in your eyes, I wanna be the [Am] light from shooting stars I wanna be [E] queen in your sweetest lies, I wanna be the [Am] love-spark in your eyes I wanna be the [E] sunshine in your eyes, I wanna be the [Am] light from shooting stars I wanna be [E] queen in your sweetest lies I wanna be the love-spark in your [Am] eyes Ay ay ay ay ay ay.</description></item><item><title>Kerijas dziesma (no mūzikla "Māsa Kerija")</title><link>http://example.org/song/1545-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Kerijas_Dziesma/</link><pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2013 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1545-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Kerijas_Dziesma/</guid><description>Dm G C Es varu jūs tik mīlēt Dm G C Šai mūžā, vai vakarā, Dm G Am Bet liktens jau mani zīlē Dm G C Un neteic ne jā, ne nē. C Em/B Likteni, likteni, F G Pažēlo, nerunā, Dm A Pažēlo, pažēlo Dm G Un pēc tam norauj masku, seja Em Am Tu, vaska bālā, F G Šai karnevālā, E Am C/G F Teic — vai tu se - ja esi, C F G Vai masku ne – si?</description></item></channel></rss>