<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>supernova on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/tags/supernova/</link><description>Recent content in supernova on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:41:13 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/supernova/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cherry Absinthe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3469-Edgars_Kreilis_McKreilis_-_Cherry_Absinthe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:41:13 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3469-Edgars_Kreilis_McKreilis_-_Cherry_Absinthe/</guid><description>I don’t remember A lot of things But the one thing I remember Is the last night of December I didn’t notice You were around How can I be so lifted At the same time feel so twisted? Oooh! I’m not fluent But the language of our love Takes me higher and above Oooh! How do you do it? ‘Cos the language of our love Takes me higher and above Oooh!</description></item><item><title>Cutting the Wire</title><link>http://example.org/song/3466-Samanta_Tina_-_Cutting_The_Wire/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:24:45 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3466-Samanta_Tina_-_Cutting_The_Wire/</guid><description>Oooo! Oooo! O! O! Oooo! Oooo! O! O! Oooo! Oooo! O! O! What if I Did not pick up High and dry With no heads up Baby Tell me there&amp;#39;s another way to see this You played me Once what a huge mistake But now it&amp;#39;s twice Don&amp;#39;t give a f*ck I won&amp;#39;t call you Sooo don&amp;#39;t pick up the phone Noooo explaining Noooo excuses I won&amp;#39;t call you Sooo don&amp;#39;t pick up the phone Oooo!</description></item><item><title>Būšu tepat</title><link>http://example.org/song/3468-Liga_Ridere_-_Busu_Tepat/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:18:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3468-Liga_Ridere_-_Busu_Tepat/</guid><description>Vai Tava sirds stostās neziņā Beidzot sāku Tevi saprast Tas ir veids, kā Tu tiec cauri tumšai ielai Skrienot ātri, neatskatoties Bet es netieku tev līdz Ja Tev ko vajadzēs, būšu tepat Te vienmēr gaidīšu, būšu tepat Pat ģimenē, Tu vienmēr biji viens Vienatnē mācījies, kas dzīve tāda ir Cīnījies par sevi pats, tā drošu vietu rast Lūk, kādēļ Tu tā skrien – neatskatoties Bet es netieku tev līdz Ja Tev ko vajadzēs, būšu tepat Tevi vienmēr gaidīšu, būšu tepat Kaut mani atstāji – te vienu tālumā Es sekošu Tev ar domām Lai kāds Tevi pasargā Tagad skatos acīs Tev Es redzu, ko meklēji Tu Mīlestība, patiesi, spēj Dziedēt vientulību Šķiet, Tu sāc soļot Jo jūtu Tevi nākam Šis būs jauns sākums Ko sirds Tev rod neziņā Ja Tev ko vajadzēs, būšu tepat Tevi vienmēr gaidīšu, būšu tepat Kaut mani atstāji – te vienu tālumā Es sekošu Tev ar domām Lai kāds Tevi pasargā Lai kāds Tevi pasargā</description></item><item><title>Awe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3463-Laime_Pilniga_-_Awe/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Feb 2019 21:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3463-Laime_Pilniga_-_Awe/</guid><description>I remember when The dream was over I felt kinda sad And now I feel so odd I need to get there back now Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, lookin’ for place to hide from you I went to my childhood place Climbed in my favourite tree in black and white Saw my beloved ones watchin’ Jim and Kurt Playin’ badminton and both them won I felt uplifted and so I flew Over the hills and the morning dew I felt so alive long ago Don’t know where I’m going but I have to go Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, looking for place to hide from you Oh, I got a secret to hold on to Oh, looking for place to hide from you Ah, I got a secret Ah, I got a secret to hold Ooh, ooh Ooh, ooh, I got a secret I got a secret to hold</description></item><item><title>Fire</title><link>http://example.org/song/3447-Double_Faced_Eels_-_Fire/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 21:34:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3447-Double_Faced_Eels_-_Fire/</guid><description>I’ve got a fire burning deep inside Illuminates my way when there’s no light Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire Never was the type to fit in / Least likely to succeed Never was the type to listen / Always marching to my own beat Never had a doubt in my mind / Ain’t got no quit in me All I’ve got’s a burning hunger / cuts and bruises to remind me Learned from my pain and heartache / turned all that into fuel All of the rage that I felt / yeah, I put in my rear-view Feel tall like the highest tower / there ain’t no stopping me All I’ve got’s a burning hunger / and voices in my head, they’re singing I’ve got a fire burning deep inside Illuminates my way when there’s no light Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire Stood on the edge of darkness / Felt my spirit breaking Thought that there&amp;#39;s no going back / My girl, my friends and family saved me Don&amp;#39;t know if I picked the right path / Or where it&amp;#39;s leading me All I&amp;#39;ve got&amp;#39;s a burning hunger / and voices in my head, they&amp;#39;re singing Whatever comes my way, I’ll be alright ‘Cause I’ve got that fire-fire-fire Got that fire-fire-fire I’ve got a fire, burning deep inside, a fire burning deep inside I’ve got a fire, burning deep inside, a fire burning deep inside I’ve got a fire</description></item><item><title>Listen to the way that I breathe</title><link>http://example.org/song/3445-Laika_Upe_-_Listen_To_The_Way_That_I_Breathe/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:56:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3445-Laika_Upe_-_Listen_To_The_Way_That_I_Breathe/</guid><description>You keep lying Eyes glued to the ceiling I keep scratching Until you come falling down from the plaster What a disaster, your stare is red Your hands are sewn to the bed The liquids that we used Are floating safe in a drain Now flush them from your brain Listen to the way that I breathe My heartbeat, the way I speak Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Listen to the way that I breathe My heartbeat, the way I speak Face the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Take the troubles on my soul Might not take back control Are you back Or just planning to attack The words you speak are sweet But somehow I see through you The demons still hold true!</description></item><item><title>Fireworks</title><link>http://example.org/song/3443-Alekss_Silvers___-_Fireworks/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Jan 2019 18:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3443-Alekss_Silvers___-_Fireworks/</guid><description>Lying in my bed of silence Know you’re gonna come tonight Thinking of the consequences Asking why Wonder if I think about you Want to know if I still care You’re the one who wants it over But we’re here This love’s incomplete It never will be But it hurts me to breathe All I care for Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn Look into my eyes and tell me Who you really wanna be Enemies, friends or lovers Who are we Said you’re staying with another But you’re always coming back Tired of being undercover Losing track This love’s incomplete It never will be But it helps me to breathe All I care for Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn This isn’t right (This isn’t right) But you’re safe for tonight (Safe for tonight) Out of sight (Out of sight) Holding me tight (Holding me tight) Tonight, you make me feel the fireworks Tonight, we’re gonna let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn Fire burn, fire burn Let this fire burn</description></item><item><title>1000 Roses</title><link>http://example.org/song/3291-Monta_Kimene_-_1000_Roses/</link><pubDate>Mon, 19 Feb 2018 12:52:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3291-Monta_Kimene_-_1000_Roses/</guid><description>When nothing happens As I’ve wanted And life has struggled in A place I shouldn’t be I take my favourite ring And put it on my finger Just to be sure If there exist any power helping me recall My strength From earth and ground Where my feet are From earth and ground Where my feet are As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses I found a letter From a man Who used to love me I didn’t know Much about it But with look Of grown eyes I know it was, it was, it was Love from heaven Love from mirror of myself Love from heaven Love from getting out of hell As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses Uh, I know he loves me still Uh, I know he loves me still, still As I lay down I smell the sweetness As I lay down I smell the sweetness As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses As I lay down I smell the sweetness Of thousand roses Of thousand roses</description></item><item><title>Lovers Bliss</title><link>http://example.org/song/3288-Lauris_Valters_-_Lovers_Bliss/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Feb 2018 15:57:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3288-Lauris_Valters_-_Lovers_Bliss/</guid><description>So there is something I really want you to know I love you darling About that I&amp;#39;m sure And when the sun rise Shining on our way Or even rainstorm Listens how we pray We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Standing in crossroads Got that feelin&amp;#39; where to go I&amp;#39;m holding you hand Our hearts are beating strong It is so simple And hard at the same time To love somebody With openly wide heart We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss We gonna stay right here We have to live like this ‘Cause there is nothing higher Than the lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss (Where ever we go) (When ever we want to be together) Where ever we go When ever we want to be together We wanna be together Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss, oh yeah Lovers bliss</description></item><item><title>Funny Girl</title><link>http://example.org/song/3274-Laura_Rizzotto_-_Funny_Girl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 18:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3274-Laura_Rizzotto_-_Funny_Girl/</guid><description>Ain’t it funny, ain’t it funny Oh, it all started as a joke But now I’m falling, now I’m falling The punch line is getting old Cause I’ve been keeping to myself For way too long, yeah Ain’t it funny, ain’t it funny I made you laugh every time we spoke I locked my heart in hesitation But somehow, you cracked the code I tore down my walls Wrecked the ceiling Ready to bare it all, but You’re looking at her, she’s looking at you I’m falling apart, what can I do To make you feel that way about me too?</description></item><item><title>Esamība</title><link>http://example.org/song/3275-Madara_Fogelmane_-_Esamiba/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 17:54:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3275-Madara_Fogelmane_-_Esamiba/</guid><description>Kad ielūkojies sevī, savā būtībā Atrodi mieru savā esamībā Nav nozīme slēpties no tā kas tevī mīt Jo, pasaulīt, izrādās Ka tur tava laime mīt Kad piemirst tas “kādēļ”, kad piemirst tas “kur” Kad piemirst tas viss, kur doties? Aizver acis un patveries savā klusumā Aiz mākoņainām gubām un skrienošām domām Gaiši zilā debess spīd, lai saule vai lietus līst Bet kad tevi rauj, rauj projām Parauj sevi atpakaļ Tā tava dzīve, tava, tava brīvība Kad piemirst tas “kādēļ”, kad piemirst tas “kur” Kad piemirst tas viss, kur doties?</description></item><item><title>Just Fine</title><link>http://example.org/song/3281-Sudden_Lights_-_Just_Fine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 17:43:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3281-Sudden_Lights_-_Just_Fine/</guid><description>Capo 3 Em Am Em G Em Am Em Em Am All alone in a crowded place Em Everyone on their way G Em Am Em Going nowhere Lawyers beggars and busy businessmen All worshipping some kind of colored Chinese paper Can cut my ears off And pull my eyes out To fit right in The more you think and calculate The more confusion there is To be left The further we go the more we forget What it was all about In the rise It sometimes it annoys to be sane In this insane world, we eat, sleep and reproduce But maybe I will be just fine And I will be just fine</description></item><item><title>Intoxicating Caramel</title><link>http://example.org/song/3205-Katrina_Gupalo_-_Intoxicating_Caramel/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 14:17:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3205-Katrina_Gupalo_-_Intoxicating_Caramel/</guid><description>Intoxicating scent sends wild flashes right in my prudence Agitating dead ends easily crashes I&amp;#39;m ready to dance Sticky caramel in both my ears Buzzing bumble-bee time disappears The feeling I&amp;#39;m 16 Indecently twisty Shakes my misty mind since he kissed me Intoxicating scent sends wild flashes right in my prudence Agitating dead ends easily crashes I&amp;#39;m ready to dance Intoxicating scent sends wild flashes right in my prudence Agitating dead ends easily crashes I&amp;#39;m ready to dance This leaky faucet Oh how can I knock it?</description></item><item><title>Heartbeat 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3138-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat_2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:52:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3138-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat_2/</guid><description>Am I know you told So many times Am So many words In different rhymes Dm C G But I don’t feel the same Am I wasn’t innocent, I know Am And things I did for sure were wrong Dm C G The time has passed so long Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am I’m getting wild when I’m alone Am I learned by heart you&amp;#39;re not my own D C Am But I never asked you to be long Am Your my desire and my pain Am But all the battles are in vain D C G You mean more than anything to me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me F You’re the one I need Am You’re the air that I breathe C Don’t throw my heart away G I want you to stay Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat</description></item><item><title>Love Injected 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3137-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected_2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3137-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected_2/</guid><description>Gm | Gm | Eb | Cm7 Gm You bring Gm/Bb The light Eb To Cm7 My darkest side, babe. Gm The day, Gm/Bb The night Eb Split Cm7 To cure the sight, oh. Gm You care, Gm/Bb You animate, Eb You guard me bare, Cm7 Bring up the heart rate. Gm Your love F Eb Revives my soul F Bb And I know Bb You&amp;#39;ll choose it whole F Eb Cm7 Overall.</description></item><item><title>Line 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</guid><description>E Ebm I&amp;#39;m going round in circles Abm F# And the door&amp;#39;s wide open E Ebm Boy I still wanna see you Abm F# Days go by, I&amp;#39;m still hoping, hoping E Where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? F# E Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? E Ebm You told me to move on Abm Searching now for somebody else F# E Ebm But baby, tell me how will I find it?</description></item><item><title>Home</title><link>http://example.org/song/3064-Euphony_-_Home/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:36:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3064-Euphony_-_Home/</guid><description>There are so many places around the world to see There are so many people to meet, but only she knows how Knows how to make me feel like I am home There are so many colours and blinding lights to see So beautiful and gracious, you know but only she knows how Knows how to make me feel like I am home Thank you for the life you gave me with your heart Thank you for your love Finally I feel like I can really start Spread my wings and fly above my fears There are so many chances to take, but I’m not sure Of disappointment later and what it’s really for, but she Knows how to make me feel like I am home, home Feels like I’m home and I’m home Thank you for the life you gave me with your heart Thank you for your love Finally I feel like I can really start Spread my wings and fly above Time goes by but there’s no place I’d rather be And I hope I found a decent melody For the song to describe how I feel About you, about love, about family Thank you for the life you gave me with your heart Thank you for your love (Thank you for your love) I can feel it’s time Spread my wings and fly above my fears</description></item><item><title>Lions</title><link>http://example.org/song/3092-Lana_Franceska_-_Lions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:23:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3092-Lana_Franceska_-_Lions/</guid><description>Silence When our words will turn to silence We’ll find the beat of love We’ll hear the beat of love Diamonds Will light up the skies and find us What we rushed to lose too fast Thinking that it would just last Lions In our hearts we’ll find our lions They’ll never let us fall They’ll guard the light that brings us home Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, like the lions that we are Sunrise We have dreamed a dream of sunrise When the morning finally comes We’ll hear the call of love Silence When our words will turn to silence We’ll find the call of love We’ll hear the call of love Lions Come and gather all my lions Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, like the lions that we are (Through the night, time by time)</description></item><item><title>Free Your Mind</title><link>http://example.org/song/3082-The_Stones_-_Free_Your_Mind/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:12:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3082-The_Stones_-_Free_Your_Mind/</guid><description>Free your mind and stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you No matter if you’re black or white, no No matter even weak or strong Free your mind and your imagination To make the choices of your own It’s up to you, but I’ll be honest We should realise somehow Just be wise and don’t be nervous Make your own decisions now So come on, keep your heart wide open Hot like oven, burning heart First of all we believe in ourselves Ready to go and ready to start Ātri gāju, ātri skrēju Ātru dzīvi dzīvodams Free your mind and stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you No matter if you’re black or white, no No matter even weak or strong Free your mind and your imagination To make the choices of your own Ātri gāju, ātri skrēju Ātru dzīvi dzīvodams Ātri gāju, ātri skrēju Ātru dzīvi dzīvodams Your dreams will come true It’s time to go through For me and for you, oh… Your dreams will come true It’s time to go through For me and for you And for me and for you, hey Free your mind and stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you No matter if you’re black or white, no No matter even weak or strong Free your mind and your imagination To make the choices of your own Ah… Let’s stop the hesitation There’s nothing else that we can do Now it’s time for celebration Of liberty and life we’ll bring to you</description></item><item><title>High Heels</title><link>http://example.org/song/3065-Riga_Metro_-_High_Heels/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:09:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3065-Riga_Metro_-_High_Heels/</guid><description>Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you Dreaming about you since the day that we met Waiting for you to call and hear you speak This is nonsense, I really don’t know you Oh boy, I really don’t know you How ’bout I give you my heart, heart Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy How ’bout I give you my heart, heart Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy Full of joy, full of hope, full of love, boy Red lips, bitchy look, high heels Is this what will make his heart beat?</description></item><item><title>Magic Years</title><link>http://example.org/song/3070-Lauris_Valters_-_Magic_Years/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:45:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3070-Lauris_Valters_-_Magic_Years/</guid><description>When this world is turning and the fire is burning I keep thinking about you, every moment, my love Can we feel much stronger and make it last longer? Flow down in this river while light is coming from above See children growing, I should be glad Is this the best we ever had? I’m looking for signs in the wind I’m looking for signs in the water I’m looking for signs on the ground I’m looking for signs in the fire When this world is turning and the fire is burning I keep thinking about you, every moment, my love Can we feel much stronger and make it last longer?</description></item><item><title>Escape</title><link>http://example.org/song/3079-Crime_Sea_-_Escape/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 09:42:54 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3079-Crime_Sea_-_Escape/</guid><description>Baby, I am so lost in this labyrinth I don’t know where is the way out of here Another animals would get lost in here They’d rather travel back to the stratosphere It’s another planet that is taking control over us Where to hide, where to go, is this even real life? It’s another planet that is taking control over us Where to hide, where to go, is this even real life?</description></item><item><title>Being A Friend</title><link>http://example.org/song/3080-Ruta_Duduma_-_Being_A_Friend/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 08:18:02 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3080-Ruta_Duduma_-_Being_A_Friend/</guid><description>Pieces falling That hold us together Chances we take That turn us for better It’s a road that never end And leads to something we call a friend And no matter how far I will know where you are I will never stop being your friend And I never will ‘Cause you’re my friend when I’m down and blue ‘Cause you’re my friend, I can count on you Your heart has turned around and I’m blessed that I know You are my friend, are my friend, I can count on you, ooh… Show them the best of you I’ll make you dare Believe me, when it’s time to go You know I will care And when the time comes for us to part Oh, I really want you to know That no matter how far I will know where you are I will never stop being your friend And I never will, oh… ‘Cause you’re my friend when I’m down and blue ‘Cause you’re my friend, I can count on you Your heart has turned around and I’m blessed that I know You are my friend, are my friend ‘Cause you’re my friend when I’m down and blue ‘Cause you’re my friend, I can count on you Your heart has turned around and I’m blessed that I know You are my friend, are my friend, you are my friend I can count on you</description></item><item><title>Look In The Mirror</title><link>http://example.org/song/3081-Paula_Dukure_-_Look_In_The_Mirror/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 08:09:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3081-Paula_Dukure_-_Look_In_The_Mirror/</guid><description>All of us have the same goal To drive the road that makes us call man pleased There’s an illusion we believe in That our happiness can be taken away Open up to what is now Take a clear look at what’s going on Is there a reason to smile Or is it time to change for the better? If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror I know I don’t have to wait long Till I’ll be free from this need To have something that gives me relief I’m learning to love life as it is Waiting for the perfect lover Who will come and make my grief go away But I know it’s too much to ask I’ll just deal with my demons alone If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror If you wanna see who can make you happy Look in the mirror I know I don’t have to wait long Till I’ll be free from this need To have something that gives me relief I’m learning to love I know I don’t have to wait long Till I’ll be free from this need To have something that gives me relief I’m learning to love life as it is Ooh yeah yeah… Till I’ll be free from this need I’m learning to love, I’m learning to love I know I don’t have to wait long I’m learning to love (Life as it is)</description></item><item><title>Choices</title><link>http://example.org/song/3089-MARTA_Marta_Grigale_-_Choices/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 07:39:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3089-MARTA_Marta_Grigale_-_Choices/</guid><description>Endless possibilities Different you, different me Lovers make and lovers break Funny how the smallest thing can alter everything Endless possibilities Different you, different me One step here and one step there You are closer now and further than you’ve ever been Every single choice you make Every single step you take The ink you leave’s indelible Choices, choices Every little word you say Every promise that you break The ink you leave’s indelible Choices, choices There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice Endless possibilities Different you, different me You can stay or walk away But you’ll never know for sure how it all would have been Every single choice you make Every single step you take The ink you leave’s indelible Choices, choices There’s always (Choices) There’s always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice There’s always, there’s always There’s always and always and always a choice</description></item><item><title>Blood Runs Quicker</title><link>http://example.org/song/2891-Katrina_Cirule_-_Blood_Runs_Quicker/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 10:44:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2891-Katrina_Cirule_-_Blood_Runs_Quicker/</guid><description>Tryna find good out of everything i do When there’s a negative it always involves you In my chest tryna break through No need to hide it No need to hide it’s true Don’t bring me down Spread across the ground Hoping that you’ll fix me I know you’re bad for me babe But my heart still flickers How can i run from you babe When my blood runs quicker I’m tryna repair the mess That we’re made But it’s hard to be positive When all we ever do is hate You’re in my head screaming my name I’m not gonna lie I’ve been trying to let you fade so Don’t bring me down Spread across the ground Hoping that you’ll fix me I know you’re bad for me babe But my heart still flickers How can i run from you babe When my blood runs quicker</description></item><item><title>Feel the Love</title><link>http://example.org/song/2894-RocknBerries_-_Feel_The_Love/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 10:23:27 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2894-RocknBerries_-_Feel_The_Love/</guid><description>I’m trying to clear the shades behind us I search for way to own your trust They’re coming up, they try to divine us All of we got turn into dust Why can’t you share what you feel? What you’re feelin’? Why can’t you feel the love that i give Why can’t you share with me what you’re feelin’? What you’re feelin’? Why can’t you feel the love that i’m givin’?</description></item><item><title>Dynamite</title><link>http://example.org/song/2885-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_Dynamite/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2017 14:39:48 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2885-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_Dynamite/</guid><description>You are setting fires in my name. You invite a moth into the flames. There’s a steep price to pay, But I know that I’ll stay. Your kind of sorcery is dangerous to me — It’s gonna blow us skyscraper high. Your sensuality is stirring something deep, Unless it’s all a trick of the night. My heart is made of dynamite, dynamite! Dynamite, dynamite! Dynamite, dynamite! I should tell myself until I learn.</description></item><item><title>Little Weird</title><link>http://example.org/song/2879-Laura_Lo_-_Little_Weird/</link><pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 20:12:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2879-Laura_Lo_-_Little_Weird/</guid><description>[C] Late night walking [Am] around in this old [F] city [G] [C] Neon lights are [Am] flashing on your [F] perfect skin [G] [C] You don’t even [Am] know that I’m watching your [F] every move [G] Just [C] talking, walking, [Am] laughing, talking - [F] round and round [G] Cause I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes Cause I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes And we [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [C] Acting silly, feeling [Am] infinite You don’t [F] want to go home [G] [C] We don’t mind what the [Am] others say Cause we’re [F] having the best time [G] tonight And I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes And I’m [Am] feeling a little [F] weird [C] looking into [G] your eyes And we [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Floating somewhere in [F] the space [C] Floating somewhere in [G] the space [Am] Floating somewhere in [F] the space [C] Floating somewhere [G] And we [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] Dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars [Am] dance with no [F] music And we [C] dream under [G] the stars</description></item><item><title>All I Know</title><link>http://example.org/song/2876-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_All_I_Know/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2017 06:50:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2876-My_Radiant_You_MyRadiantU_-_All_I_Know/</guid><description>[C] I Left my home on a Sunday Hear the church bells ringing [Am] Got in my car started driving Driving till the end of road [C] I&amp;#39;ll send my love to you baby From a thousand miles away [Am] It&amp;#39;s like the water is rising And sky&amp;#39;s about to break All I [C] know You made me for a [Am] reason All I [F] know I find myself on my [G] knees again And now you want me to [C] stay I know you want me to [Am] stay Hey, hey!</description></item><item><title>Line</title><link>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</guid><description>I’m going [F] round in [Em] circles And the [Am] door’s wide [G] open Boy I [F] still wanna see [Em] you Days go [Am] by, I’m still hoping, [G] hoping [F] Where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? [G] Tell me, baby, [F] where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? You [F] told me to move [Em] on Searching [Am] now for somebody else But baby, [G] tell me [F] how will I find [Em] it?</description></item><item><title>I'm In Love With You</title><link>http://example.org/song/2868-The_Ludvig_-_Im_In_Love_With_You/</link><pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2017 17:08:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2868-The_Ludvig_-_Im_In_Love_With_You/</guid><description>[Am] It&amp;#39;s late in the evening [C] And I&amp;#39;m waiting for you [Am] Soon I&amp;#39;ll stop breathing [C] And I blame it on the full moon So [F] darling, please [G] believe I&amp;#39;m in love with [C] you [Am] Leave your shoes at the door [C] I can&amp;#39;t wait no more [Am] We might be too young [C] But I think we&amp;#39;re in love. So [F] darling, please [G] believe I&amp;#39;m in love with [C] you [F] Time flies by [G] your eyes [Am] When I am with you I [C] feel alive</description></item><item><title>Damnation</title><link>http://example.org/song/2574-Catalepsia_-_Damnation/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2016 11:40:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2574-Catalepsia_-_Damnation/</guid><description>[Am] Look through my [F] mind It’s a [C] world of con[E]fusion [Am] There&amp;#39;s nothing [F] right to see There’s [C] nothing true to [E] feel [Am] Run, I am [F] cursed Your [C] spell won’t [E] save me My [Am] world is dark and [F] bleak My [C] heart is still and [E] cold [Am] Speak to my [F] soul It’s a [C] voice of the non-[E] existent There’s [Am] nothing to [F] understand There’s [C] nothing fair for [E] you [Am] I am too far, too [F] deep You will [C] never reach my [E] soul [Am] Stay away from [F] me You [C] cannot make it [E] real [Am] I’m too close to [F] fall From the [C] heaven of your [E] dream [Am] Say goodbye to me [F] dear I’m [C] leaving you be[E]hind [Am] Look through your [F] mind It’s a [C] world of destruc[E]tion [Am] There’s nothing to [F] memorize There’s [C] nothing bright for [E] me [Am] Speak to your [F] soul It’s a [C] voice of fading [E] prayer [Am] There’s nothing [F] to revive There’s [C] nothing I can [E] change [Am] I am too far, too [F] deep You will [C] never reach my [E] soul [Am] Stay away from [F] me You [C] cannot make it [E] real [Am] I’m too close to [F] fall From the [C] heaven of your [E] dream [Am] Say goodbye to me [F] dear I’m [C] leaving you be[E]hind</description></item><item><title>Heartbeat</title><link>http://example.org/song/2549-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2549-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat/</guid><description>[Am] I know you told So many times [Am] So many words In different rhymes But [D] i don’t [F] feel the [G] same [Am] I wasn’t innocent, i know [Am] And things i did for sure were wrong The [D] time has [F] passed so [G] long Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me [Am] I’m getting wild when i’m alone [Am] I learned by heart youre not my own But [D] i never [F] asked you to be[G]long [Am] Your my desire and my pain [Am] But all the battles are in vain You [D] mean more [F] than anything to [G] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me [D] You’re the one i need You’re the [F] air that i breath [D] Don’t throw my heart away I want you to [E] stay Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat</description></item><item><title>I Can</title><link>http://example.org/song/2519-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_I_Can/</link><pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2016 22:12:30 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2519-Markus_Riva_Mikelis_Laksa_-_I_Can/</guid><description>One more day, one more night Hard to say what’s on my mind I tried, I tried Every thought on my mind Makes me feel that love is blind This time, this time I will follow, follow you I will follow, follow you I can, I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again Then the storms that we survive They let me back to life I tried, you know that I tried Now that you are next to me I can feel infinity again I feel alive I will follow, follow you I will follow, follow you I can, I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again I can, yes I can I can, I can see you again I can, yes I can I can I will follow, follow you I will follow, follow you I can, I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again I can almost feel the sea I can do anything to see you again Yes I can, I can write your memories ‘Cause that is all we need to stay alive And I really wanna see you again.</description></item><item><title>Love injected</title><link>http://example.org/song/2175-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2175-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected/</guid><description>[Em] You bring [G] the light [C] to my darkest [Am] side, babe [Em] The day, [G] the night [C] split to cure the [Am] sight, ooh [Em] You care, [G] you animate [C] You guard me bare, [Am] bring up the heart rate Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] [Em] Your eye’s a good mirror, [G] look under the cover [C] Love is above [Am] all [Em] I’m safe into your hands [G] Let’s move away, [C] the edges ex[Am]pand Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] Show me the [Em] source of the light, I’m becoming [C] affected Seeing the [Em] glow of the white is what I have de[C]tected Feeling [Em] again I’m alive, it’s your shining re[C]flected Love in[Em]jected, love in[C]jected Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] [Em][G][C][Am] Oh, oh, oh, oh Oh, oh, oh, oh.</description></item></channel></rss>