<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Patrisha on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/patrisha/</link><description>Recent content in Patrisha on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 18:07:44 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/patrisha/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hush</title><link>http://example.org/song/4986-Patrisha_-_Hush/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Feb 2023 18:07:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4986-Patrisha_-_Hush/</guid><description>Hey, I fly easy in the wind Even with a heavy rain I can elevate Teardrops of pain Rain on me, oh Set me free from this bottomless pit I wanna go To my castle in blue print It&amp;#39;s waiting for me, mmm If I make it seem like it&amp;#39;s not easy For me to show my soul It&amp;#39;s my way of saying to you That I&amp;#39;m just a broken girl Hush, hush Baby, don&amp;#39;t you cry Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Hush, hush Baby, don&amp;#39;t you cry Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Hush, hush Baby, don&amp;#39;t you cry Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Hush, hush Baby, don&amp;#39;t you cry Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Promise there will be no bad blood Mirror me Let me into your sins The devil wears Prada I wear it like my skin And all the chaos within Meet me halfway Tell me where to go Change our sense of time And let delusion grow We&amp;#39;re gliding slow If I make it seem like it&amp;#39;s not easy For me to show my soul Hush, hush Baby, don&amp;#39;t you cry Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Hush, hush Baby, don&amp;#39;t you cry Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Promise you won&amp;#39;t fall in love Hush, hush, hush Hush, hush, hush Hush, hush, hush Hush, hush, hush</description></item><item><title>Jūtas nolietotas</title><link>http://example.org/song/4822-Patrisha_-_Jutas_Nolietotas/</link><pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2021 17:42:58 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4822-Patrisha_-_Jutas_Nolietotas/</guid><description>G#m B Es atkal visu nakti domās, pārdomāšu daudz F# G#m Gulēt neiešu, kad mēness, katru reizi jauns Varbūt visu nakti skumšu, kad nenojaut Un varbūt labi arī mazliet, kad pasāpēt man ļauts Piedz. G#m B Nolietotas, jūtas nolietotas F# Beidzies derīguma laiks G#m Nebūs atgriešanās vairs. Tavos sapņos grūti dzīvot Tu neļauj piecelties Labāk vienam būt un lidot Un no augšas skatīties Tik grūti tevi izdzēst No domām izsvītrot Bet laiks liekas domas izmest Par daudz ir izdzīvots Piedz.</description></item><item><title>Clock</title><link>http://example.org/song/4091-Patrisha_-_Clock/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 20:28:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4091-Patrisha_-_Clock/</guid><description>A clock is ticking around, around, around. It is saying tick tock, tick tock ,tick tock. A clock is screaming it’s time, it’s time, it’s time. Clock, clock, clock is saying tick tock. Every day, every night, Second by second, hour by hour, Day by day, night by night, All my life it’s screaming the time. A clock is climbing up and up the wall. It is saying tick tock, tick tock, tick tock.</description></item><item><title>Es Varu Būt Tā</title><link>http://example.org/song/3523-Patrisha_-_Es_Varu_But_Ta/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 May 2019 15:53:35 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3523-Patrisha_-_Es_Varu_But_Ta/</guid><description>Em D Es varu būt tā, kura nāk, kad tev skumji C7 Kad pārgājis negaiss, kas mierināt māk Em D Es varu būt tā, kura turēs pie rokas C Ar kuru tu iesi, kur robežu nav Em D Es varu būt tā, kura smaržo pēc lietus C Un no it nekā, kura nebaidās vairs Em D Es varu būt tā, kura sajauks tev prātu C Es varu būt tā, kurai nav nekas svēts Piedz.</description></item></channel></rss>