<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Andris Ērglis on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/andris-%C4%93rglis/</link><description>Recent content in Andris Ērglis on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:16:14 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/andris-%C4%93rglis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Laime manās rokās</title><link>http://example.org/song/3843-Andris_Erglis_-_Laime_Manas_Rokas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jun 2020 08:16:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3843-Andris_Erglis_-_Laime_Manas_Rokas/</guid><description>Kā gan tā var - mani iemīt dubļos Un pret zvaizgznēm samainīt? Kā gan tā var - ignorēt un atstumt - Vēl nav pusseši, ir tikai trīs?! Piedz. Paliks laime manās rokās, Kamēr es tai nepieskaršos. Vai tā būsi Tu vai cita, Pateikšu Tev pusdesmitos. Salstu te viens jau pusotru stundu, Sarkanas rozes rokās man trīs. Kā gan tā var pedantiski kavēt, Runāts bij vienos - nu jau ir trīs. Piedz.</description></item><item><title>Broken Lullaby</title><link>http://example.org/song/3370-Andris_Erglis_-_Broken_Lullaby/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 20:47:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3370-Andris_Erglis_-_Broken_Lullaby/</guid><description>You call my name, but I was deaf and blind I lost myself when I was deep in mind No, I didn’t hear you cry, and I wonder why Someone plays this dozy lullaby You call my name, words scatter like the leaves On empty streets they’ve gone and disappeared No, I didn’t say you lied, but I wonder why We can’t stop this endless lullaby I am your old imaginary friend I am your road going to the end I am your dream, and time is always passing by I am your last broken lullaby You call my name, but there was just no sound The doors are closed with no escape around Oh, I wanted no reply, but I wonder why Someone ever wrote this lullaby I am your old imaginary friend I am your road going to the end I am your dream, and time is always passing by I am your last broken lullaby (I am your old imaginary friend I am your road) going, going to the end I am your dream, and time is always passing by I am your last broken lullaby</description></item><item><title>Izvēlies</title><link>http://example.org/song/1387-Andris_Erglis_-_Izvelies/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2012 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1387-Andris_Erglis_-_Izvelies/</guid><description>Oriģināls sākas ar D Ievads C Am F C (Bb-C) (Bb) C Am Pasaulē- viens otram mēs starp &amp;#34;jā&amp;#34; un &amp;#34;nē&amp;#34; F C Kad pūlī Tu vai vienatnē- izvēlies! Bb C Am Starp to- ko jānojauc vai jālabo- F C paņem visu labāko- vai neko Bb Gm Un kad pati sev Tu atbildēsi- es būšu tavs jautājums Bb G Kad Tu pati sevi saprast spēsi- tad varēsim runāt par &amp;#34;mums&amp;#34; Piedz.</description></item></channel></rss>