<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Ivo Grīsniņš-Grīslis on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/ivo-gr%C4%ABsni%C5%86%C5%A1-gr%C4%ABslis/</link><description>Recent content in Ivo Grīsniņš-Grīslis on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 13:10:08 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/ivo-gr%C4%ABsni%C5%86%C5%A1-gr%C4%ABslis/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Ietin mani</title><link>http://example.org/song/4779-Ivo_Grisnins-Grislis_-_Ietin_Mani/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Feb 2021 13:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4779-Ivo_Grisnins-Grislis_-_Ietin_Mani/</guid><description>Ietin mani, ietin tā Kamēr abi divi kā zāles stiebri Vieni klajumā Slēpjamies kā grēcinieki. Ietin mani, ietin tā Savij savas rokas ap mani tik cieši Prieka palagā, Nemelošu, teikšu tieši</description></item><item><title>Cinderella</title><link>http://example.org/song/3324-Ivo_Grisnins-Grislis_-_Cinderella/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:23:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3324-Ivo_Grisnins-Grislis_-_Cinderella/</guid><description>Once upon a time lived a girl With a honey blonde hair and eyes like pearls With a heart like a diamond and pristine soul She was pretty indeed And then came a day she went to a party Beautifully dressed, excited she was How to behave and how to look smarty If prince is asking to dance Would you be my lady Cinderella? Would you play the game and dance with me I would be your prince until the midnight Let us happen what used to be Dancing was short and then came a midnight Tears in her eyes ’cause she had to leave Way through the night leads to a daylight Hard for her to believe Would you be my lady Cinderella?</description></item><item><title>Because I Love You</title><link>http://example.org/song/3347-Ivo_Grisnins-Grislis_-_Because_I_Love_You/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:15:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3347-Ivo_Grisnins-Grislis_-_Because_I_Love_You/</guid><description>If somebody gave me a million, I’d give a second half of it to you My mind changes like a chameleon and that’s the way I do But I love you in the way I do If I could write a really nice poem I would dedicate it to you Women can’t live without them and that’s the way they do But I love you in the way I do Because I love you in the way I do If I would be a perfect person I wouldn’t be interesting for you Because no one in this world is perfect, not they, not me nor you And you love me in the way you do And I love you in the way I do And I love you in the way I do And you love me in the way you do And I love you in the way I do</description></item></channel></rss>