<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Madara Celma on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/madara-celma/</link><description>Recent content in Madara Celma on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 19:18:23 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/madara-celma/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Away from You</title><link>http://example.org/song/3373-Madara_Celma_-_Away_From_You/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 19:18:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3373-Madara_Celma_-_Away_From_You/</guid><description>I wish I could runaway from you Like a bird in the sky and feel nothing for you But as days go by, on and on somehow My soul is still waiting for you Oh, my soul is still waiting for you I wish I could runaway from you Like a bird in the sky and feel nothing for you But as days go by, on and on somehow My soul is still waiting for you Oh, my soul is still waiting for you Promises broken and words left unspoken But with sorrow my life goes so wrong Do you miss me?</description></item><item><title>I Might Be the One</title><link>http://example.org/song/3099-Madara_Celma_-_I_Might_Be_The_One/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 10:15:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3099-Madara_Celma_-_I_Might_Be_The_One/</guid><description>You may close, close every door if you dare You may turn, turn out the lights And pretend you’re not there You can try to forget about me, but please Stop before you do ‘Cause I might be your only shelter Might be the one who always stands for you All you have to do is call my name in silence And I will run to you like I have wings I don’t and I won’t believe that you’re gonna leave Look at me, stay with me Feel the flame burning in me, in your eyes Still I can see how much you need me Please, stop before you go ‘Cause I might be your only shelter Might be the one who always stands for you All you have to do is call my name in silence And I will run to you like I have wings ‘Cause I might be your only shelter Might be the one who always stands for you All you have to do is call my name in silence And I will run to you like I have wings You gave me wings</description></item><item><title>Elpa</title><link>http://example.org/song/1870-Madara_Celma_-_Elpa/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 11:39:38 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1870-Madara_Celma_-_Elpa/</guid><description>Tu nesmejies, ja dzirdi mani raudam Un neaizej, ja sirds man sāpēs kliedz Aizver durvis un paliec, kaut uz brīdi kavējies, neaizej! Aizver durvis un paliec, kaut uz brīdi kavējies. Es, vēlos saprast ik katru vārdu, ik katru domu savās tīt. Tavu elpu sadzirdēt tik tuvu savai, lai ir bail pazaudēt. Tavu elpu sadzirdēt tik tuvu savai, lai ir bail pazaudēt. Un Tavu sirdi sajust cauri manai un atļaut sev noticēt.</description></item><item><title>Dziesma par Tevi</title><link>http://example.org/song/1868-Madara_Celma_-_Dziesma_Par_Tevi/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 11:39:21 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1868-Madara_Celma_-_Dziesma_Par_Tevi/</guid><description>Man dziesma par tevi, pusbalsī aiznesta vējā skan. Sekundes lēni tālāk rit, bet stundas skrien neprātā. Tu nesauc vēl mani, nemeklē glāstus, kas maigi līst. Es atrodu tevi pusnaktī un paņemu līdz rītausmā. Tev glāsti lēni, kā stundas tālāk vēl rit, un aiznes vējā mani, pār nakti lēnām, kas krīt. Tev glāsti lēni, kā stundas tālāk vēl rit un aiznes vējā mani, pār nakti lēnām, kas krīt. Tu nejautā man, kas notiks rīt, tu nejautā man neko.</description></item><item><title>Ar lietu dejot</title><link>http://example.org/song/1867-Madara_Celma_-_Ar_Lietu_Dejot/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2014 11:39:14 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1867-Madara_Celma_-_Ar_Lietu_Dejot/</guid><description>[C] Ar lietu [F] dejot, [G] vējā sildī[C]ties, [C] caur nakti [F] ticēt, uz [G] rītu paļau[C]ties. [C] Par vienu [F] domāt, ar [G] otru aizmir[C]sties, [C] caur melnām [F] naktīm, pie [G] rītiem atgrie[C]zties. [C] Ar vienu [F] skūpstu par [G] otru maksāts [C] tiek, [C] ar pieskā[F]rienu tev [G] vienu nepie[C]tiek. [C] Tu lietū [F] dejo un [G] vējā sasil[C]dies, [C] caur nakti [F] tici, uz [G] rītu paļau[C]jies.</description></item></channel></rss>