<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Triānas Parks (Triana Park) on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/tri%C4%81nas-parks-triana-park/</link><description>Recent content in Triānas Parks (Triana Park) on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:05:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/tri%C4%81nas-parks-triana-park/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Kā Gaisa Balonā</title><link>http://example.org/song/3980-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Ka_Gaisa_Balona/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 15:05:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3980-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Ka_Gaisa_Balona/</guid><description>Diena nāk, un rokas Tavas rimst Man par sevi vēlreiz jāpiedzimst. Šoreiz nevar apskaut, apturēt Vieglām kustībām mani slāpēt. Ļauj man sākt un vārdos sapīties Kājām gaisām laiks ir apstājies Ja Tu spēsi pirmais projām iet, Smalkām kustībām, kas mani tur ciet Negaisa mākonī kā gaisa balonā Kāds mani līdzi sauc Bet Tu nelaid tālāk (tālāk) Negaisa mākonī kā gaisa balonā Kāds mani līdzi sauc Bet Tu nelaid tālāk Kā lai saprot, kā lai iztulko, Mana sirds vairs tevi nesaprot Pats tu nāci, pats nu projām ej Kā aiziet ledus upē Lietus manu laimi lej.</description></item><item><title>Kamēr</title><link>http://example.org/song/3578-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Kamer/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Feb 2020 18:52:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3578-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Kamer/</guid><description>Dm Tu vēl neesi redzējis visu. Tu vēl neesi redzējis kâ Gm7 upes griežas virpuļos, mēļo Salacā. Am7 Am To nevar izstāstīt. Gm Tu vēl neesi redzējis visu. Dm Tu vēl neesi redzējis visu. Tu vēl neesi redzējis kâ Gm7 meža zaļo segu klāj kāds debesu molbertā. Am7 Am Tu vēl neesi redzējis visu. Gm7 Gm Tikai lūdzu atgriezies. Piedz. 2x Gm Kamēr, kamēr, kamēr Bb Dm Gm debess vāli veļas kamolos, Gm kamēr, kamēr, kamēr Dm F Gm Dm soli spers kāds, klusi atskatos, bet tevis tur nav.</description></item><item><title>Lullaby for My Dreammate (Diamond Lullaby)</title><link>http://example.org/song/3337-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Lullaby_For_My_Dreammate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:03:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3337-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Lullaby_For_My_Dreammate/</guid><description>I’ll be a little bird that sits by your side I’ll wonder how you taste and what is inside In your little heart I’ll be powder of the sun that you never see I will touch your hair whenever wind carries me to you I will be your temple when you are at home I will shine the stars so you won’t feel alone I will tell the storm to go back where it laid So you won’t be afraid So you won’t be afraid You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me You can just dream another dream of me</description></item><item><title>Call Me Any Time You Need a Problem</title><link>http://example.org/song/3349-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Call_Me_Any_Time_You_Need_A_Problem/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:00:20 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3349-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Call_Me_Any_Time_You_Need_A_Problem/</guid><description>You’re only joking in your own skin You’re only losing everything you’ve got within You’re feeling like you wanna get out You’re feeling like you wanna get in I see you’re feeling low, like a mouse in a cage I see you’re feeling low, like an actor with no stage I see the problem, I see the cause I am the problem, that’s what you’re feeling insecure I am the problem, I am the cause Of your never-ending tricks with your thousand little whores I am the devil living in your little head I am the nightmare waiting in your cosy bed I am the problem I am the problem I am the problem I am the problem I see you’re feeling low, like a mouse in a cage I see you’re feeling low, like an actor with no stage I see the problem, I see the cause I am the problem, that’s what you’re feeling insecure I am the problem I am the problem I am the problem I am the problem Your black heart is so cruel Love is not just a tool Black as charcoal, it’s cake I’m your sweetest mistake I am the problem, I am the cause Of your never-ending tricks with your thousand little whores I am the devil living in your little head I am the nightmare waiting in your cosy bed I am the problem, problem, problem (I am the problem) I am the thing you seek (I am the problem) Call me anytime you need (I am the problem) I am the thing you seek (I am the problem) Call me anytime you need (I am the problem) I am the thing you seek (I am the problem) Call me anytime you need (I am the problem) I am the thing you seek (I am the problem) Call me anytime Call me anytime you need a problem</description></item><item><title>Bye Bye</title><link>http://example.org/song/3331-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Bye_Bye/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 20:43:44 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3331-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Bye_Bye/</guid><description>Daddy stay away, mother please don’t cry I wanna feel the steam and I wanna fly high I wanna do the things that I never did, no I wanna feel the rhythm of the big brand show, so I just wanna live I just wanna go bye bye I just wanna live I just wanna go bye bye Too many names there are on the display Too many different words I don’t know which way They lead me, they guide me, I move too slow I really, really, really, really got to go, so I just wanna live I just wanna go bye bye I just wanna live I just wanna go bye bye This is not a game, this is not a show, no This is a reality where things come and go This is not a game, this is not a show, no This is a reality where things come and go I just wanna know I just wanna go bye bye I just wanna live I just wanna go bye bye I just wanna live I just wanna live I just wanna live, I wanna see the world I wanna feel the brightness of enlightenment of the mind Millions of people live in Hong Kong We are standing on together singing different song Tomorrow sun is coming to take us away Tomorrow I am going to learn how to play, so I just wanna know, I just wanna know why, why I just wanna leave, I just wanna go bye bye I just wanna know, I just wanna know why, why I just wanna leave, I just wanna go bye bye</description></item><item><title>Line 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</guid><description>E Ebm I&amp;#39;m going round in circles Abm F# And the door&amp;#39;s wide open E Ebm Boy I still wanna see you Abm F# Days go by, I&amp;#39;m still hoping, hoping E Where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? F# E Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? E Ebm You told me to move on Abm Searching now for somebody else F# E Ebm But baby, tell me how will I find it?</description></item><item><title>Line</title><link>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</guid><description>I’m going [F] round in [Em] circles And the [Am] door’s wide [G] open Boy I [F] still wanna see [Em] you Days go [Am] by, I’m still hoping, [G] hoping [F] Where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? [G] Tell me, baby, [F] where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? You [F] told me to move [Em] on Searching [Am] now for somebody else But baby, [G] tell me [F] how will I find [Em] it?</description></item><item><title>Laika dziesmiņa</title><link>http://example.org/song/2429-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Laika_Dziesmina/</link><pubDate>Sun, 20 Dec 2015 08:17:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2429-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Laika_Dziesmina/</guid><description>D A 4X D A D A Ir tik grūti piecelties D A D A Ja tev nav uz kā, kur atsperties D A Laimes māte tevi atstājusi D A Bm Pasaulē, kur katrs iet uz savu pusi D Mmm A D A D A Uz savu pusi D A D D A D A Arī saule norimsies D A D A Un jauna zvaigzne kaut kur iedegsies D A Visi vēji mostās tavā pusē F#m Bm Manā pasaulē tu vienmēr smaidot klusē D Kāpēc tu klusē?</description></item></channel></rss>