<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Ārzemnieki on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/%C4%81rzemnieki/</link><description>Recent content in Ārzemnieki on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:37:29 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/%C4%81rzemnieki/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cauri Grobiņai</title><link>http://example.org/song/4024-Arzemnieki_-_Cauri_Grobinai/</link><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 16:37:29 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4024-Arzemnieki_-_Cauri_Grobinai/</guid><description>Daži dzīvo laukos, daži pilsētā. Daži pat nekad nav bijuš&amp;#39; Lietuvā. Katram ir savs celš un savas pieturas, Bet ir tā viena vieta, kas katram parādās. Es domāju, ka šis ir dzīves liktenis, Ka katram reiz ir jābrauc, katram reiz ir jābrauc... 2x Cauri grobiņai, cauri Grobiņai, Cauri grobiņai, cauri, cauri When I first came to Latvia, I wondered where to go. They said a place called Liepāja was wonderful. And since I&amp;#39;m here some weeks, I&amp;#39;m thinking to go home.</description></item><item><title>Cake to Bake</title><link>http://example.org/song/2546-Arzemnieki_-_Cake_To_Bake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2546-Arzemnieki_-_Cake_To_Bake/</guid><description>Capo 1 Intro: F Dm F Dm F I melted the ice of the polar caps Dm Found the raiders of the lost ark C Solved a case for the genius from Baker Street F Helped to clean the Central Park Dm I created the plan for the Chinese wall Gm Went to desert, made it rain Am Swam through a shark tank bloodily F Found Atlantis, by the way C But today F Bb I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Bb Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku G C Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep F I talked to a unicorn the other night Dm Took me up on a lonely star C Did the moonwalk on the milky way F Realized I&amp;#39;ve gone too far Dm So I questioned the law of gravity Gm Put the apple back up to the apple tree Am Ej tu nost: I even learned Latvian F I know it&amp;#39;s so hard to believe C But today F Bb I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Bb Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku G C Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku F Bb We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Am Bb C Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, wait for it F Am Bb C Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, wait for it F A Dm Bb Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, have some cake F C F Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake F Bb We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Garšīgi.</description></item></channel></rss>