<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Lana Frančeska on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/lana-fran%C4%8Deska/</link><description>Recent content in Lana Frančeska on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 15:09:17 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/lana-fran%C4%8Deska/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>100 gramu sapņu</title><link>http://example.org/song/4318-Lana_Franceska_-_100_Gramu_Sapnu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jun 2020 15:09:17 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/4318-Lana_Franceska_-_100_Gramu_Sapnu/</guid><description>Ieģērbusies abos savos laimes kreklos Karājos nu rāmi bezdibenim pāri. Iekrītu es viņā, mīļā sirdsapziņā. Lēni dīgstu tagad viņa zemapziņā. Iedodiet man vēl simts gramu sapņu, Aulēkšos, lai varu es pa galaktikām laist. Visi draugi teiks: „Ak mīļā, tas tak par traku!” Bet acīm ciet es apņēmusies laimes zvaigzni skaut. O-o-o ... laimes zvaigzni skaut O-o-o .... apņēmusies es Noķeru es Tevi, mazo nerātneli, Kad tu zvaigznes zagi, domājot par mani.</description></item><item><title>Lions</title><link>http://example.org/song/3092-Lana_Franceska_-_Lions/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2017 10:23:10 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3092-Lana_Franceska_-_Lions/</guid><description>Silence When our words will turn to silence We’ll find the beat of love We’ll hear the beat of love Diamonds Will light up the skies and find us What we rushed to lose too fast Thinking that it would just last Lions In our hearts we’ll find our lions They’ll never let us fall They’ll guard the light that brings us home Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, like the lions that we are Sunrise We have dreamed a dream of sunrise When the morning finally comes We’ll hear the call of love Silence When our words will turn to silence We’ll find the call of love We’ll hear the call of love Lions Come and gather all my lions Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, through the time We’ll stand hand in hand, we’ll fight side by side Through the night, like the lions that we are (Through the night, time by time)</description></item><item><title>Es tevi dzirdu</title><link>http://example.org/song/2195-Lana_Franceska_-_Es_Tevi_Dzirdu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Jun 2015 08:38:18 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2195-Lana_Franceska_-_Es_Tevi_Dzirdu/</guid><description>Ieģērbusies abos savos laimes kreklos Karājos nu rāmi bezdibenim pāri. Iekrītu es viņā, mīļā sirdsapziņā. Lēni dīgstu tagad viņa zemapziņā. Iedodiet man vēl simts gramu sapņu, Aulēkšos, lai varu es pa galaktikām laist. Visi draugi teiks: „Ak mīļā, tas tak par traku!” Bet acīm ciet es apņēmusies laimes zvaigzni skaut. O-o-o ... laimes zvaigzni skaut O-o-o .... apņēmusies es Noķeru es Tevi, mazo nerātneli, Kad tu zvaigznes zagi, domājot par mani.</description></item></channel></rss>