<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>eurovision on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/tags/eurovision/</link><description>Recent content in eurovision on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 19:34:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/tags/eurovision/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>All You Know</title><link>http://example.org/song/3307-C-Stones_-_All_You_Know/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 19:34:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3307-C-Stones_-_All_You_Know/</guid><description>Let’s go! Hey everybody, time’s up, we’re here, C-Stones, come on! All we’re hearing and all we say Now, then and everyday, You, you get up, up and up you find, yeah, That different standing downward sign. All you know is endless love there above, You’ve said so, As you go and search for more forbidden doors, You’ve said so. Oh baby, and you will live forever, Oh baby, if you want it, Oh baby, and I will give you all that, Oh baby, what do you feel and all you want.</description></item><item><title>Hey, Boy, Follow Me</title><link>http://example.org/song/3311-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Hey_Boy_Follow_Me/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 18:30:09 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3311-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_Hey_Boy_Follow_Me/</guid><description>There are so many places, so many things to see So many different faces, but, baby, look at me I know the scenic mountain where you would go uphill So I know we start dreaming of some vicious devil feel But if you let me lead you because you want to know Don’t hesitate, my darling, just take my hand and go Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide ‘Cause when we walk across my world you’ll be my guiding light You have to hear my ocean, to see my land is wide To feel my deep devotion, experience my light But if you think a stranger is better guiding you I’ll try to understand that if I’m a stranger, too But if you let me lead you because you want to know Don’t hesitate, my darling, just take my hand and go Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide ‘Cause when we walk across my world you’ll be my guiding light Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide ‘Cause when we walk across my world you’ll be my guiding light Hey, boy, follow me if you want to see the sky Hey, boy, follow me, baby, just you and I Hey, boy, follow me, I’ll be your happy guide So, baby, follow-up all on me to be my guiding light</description></item><item><title>Funny Girl</title><link>http://example.org/song/3274-Laura_Rizzotto_-_Funny_Girl/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Feb 2018 18:11:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3274-Laura_Rizzotto_-_Funny_Girl/</guid><description>Ain’t it funny, ain’t it funny Oh, it all started as a joke But now I’m falling, now I’m falling The punch line is getting old Cause I’ve been keeping to myself For way too long, yeah Ain’t it funny, ain’t it funny I made you laugh every time we spoke I locked my heart in hesitation But somehow, you cracked the code I tore down my walls Wrecked the ceiling Ready to bare it all, but You’re looking at her, she’s looking at you I’m falling apart, what can I do To make you feel that way about me too?</description></item><item><title>Heartbeat 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3138-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat_2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:52:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3138-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat_2/</guid><description>Am I know you told So many times Am So many words In different rhymes Dm C G But I don’t feel the same Am I wasn’t innocent, I know Am And things I did for sure were wrong Dm C G The time has passed so long Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am I’m getting wild when I’m alone Am I learned by heart you&amp;#39;re not my own D C Am But I never asked you to be long Am Your my desire and my pain Am But all the battles are in vain D C G You mean more than anything to me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me F You’re the one I need Am You’re the air that I breathe C Don’t throw my heart away G I want you to stay Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat C That&amp;#39;s what I want G That&amp;#39;s what I need Am Feeling again that you&amp;#39;re breathing with me Am Feeling your heartbeat</description></item><item><title>Love Injected 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3137-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected_2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2017 11:40:16 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3137-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected_2/</guid><description>Gm | Gm | Eb | Cm7 Gm You bring Gm/Bb The light Eb To Cm7 My darkest side, babe. Gm The day, Gm/Bb The night Eb Split Cm7 To cure the sight, oh. Gm You care, Gm/Bb You animate, Eb You guard me bare, Cm7 Bring up the heart rate. Gm Your love F Eb Revives my soul F Bb And I know Bb You&amp;#39;ll choose it whole F Eb Cm7 Overall.</description></item><item><title>Line 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</link><pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2017 11:38:39 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3131-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line_2/</guid><description>E Ebm I&amp;#39;m going round in circles Abm F# And the door&amp;#39;s wide open E Ebm Boy I still wanna see you Abm F# Days go by, I&amp;#39;m still hoping, hoping E Where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? F# E Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? Ebm Abm Tell me, baby, where we draw the line? E Ebm You told me to move on Abm Searching now for somebody else F# E Ebm But baby, tell me how will I find it?</description></item><item><title>Here We Go</title><link>http://example.org/song/3006-PeR_-_Here_We_Go/</link><pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 12:46:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3006-PeR_-_Here_We_Go/</guid><description>Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Ladies and Gentlemen, I need a starlight &amp;#39;Cause I never had a day without a fight I slid through the darkness, it took me to a height Of a lonesome, cold and never ending night I&amp;#39;m the man on the moon, call me Andy Kaufman There are demons inside me but I&amp;#39;m stomp&amp;#39;em I know I can be an unstoppable force I try, me, let me take a walk on the bright side Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly A lot of thoughts in my head keep pulling me down So many guests in my house I could not notice the sound Of the doorbell telling they&amp;#39;re about to come I&amp;#39;m surrounded by problems, I got to run (But no) I keep pulling myself up (But no) I keep pulling myself up I&amp;#39;m on a mission to fulfill my vision All day, everyday, never ever, ever give up Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly Here we [C] go, here we [F] go Here we [C] go, here we [F] go So alive, in the sky, we can [C] Fly</description></item><item><title>Beautiful Song</title><link>http://example.org/song/3004-Anmary_-_Beautiful_Song/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2017 18:50:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3004-Anmary_-_Beautiful_Song/</guid><description>Intro: F C G Am F C G Am Am Am I was born in distant 1980 C G the year that Irish Johnny Logan won F C/Am thirty years ago, they still remember F so dream away C today&amp;#39;s the day G Am I&amp;#39;m singing out my song Am When I join this grand parade of winners C G and we&amp;#39;ve made this song a worldwide hit F C/Am I will buy oh my own mike to sing in F and all the jobs C I&amp;#39;ve had before G Am I&amp;#39;m surely gonna quit F C G Am Beautiful song is on the radio, is in the tv shows and plays on and on F C G Am beautiful song that everybody hums and everybody loves Am My Mom said I&amp;#39;d grow up to be a singer C G And Daddy smiled when gave me my guitar F C/Am I do my best, and I&amp;#39;ll be so much better F C G Am Brightest of the highest and the farthest of the stars Am And on that day when Sir Mick Jagger phones me C G Tell him, please, that I am very busy F C/Am writing brand new songs with Paul McCartney F C G So sorry Mick, I&amp;#39;ll call you back, someday I&amp;#39;ll call Am you back.</description></item><item><title>I Hear Your Heart</title><link>http://example.org/song/2895-Cosmos_-_I_Hear_Your_Heart/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2017 17:38:42 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2895-Cosmos_-_I_Hear_Your_Heart/</guid><description>In a world that is beeping and blaring Growing louder every day I cover my ears But none of the noise will go away Sirens, Barking dogs Thank God for the one and only sound that turns it around and makes it right I hear your heart Whisprin’ to me No matter where I may happen to be Sending me love and shining it through I hear your heart Can you hear mine too?</description></item><item><title>Line</title><link>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</link><pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2017 12:10:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2873-Trianas_Parks_Triana_Park_-_Line/</guid><description>I’m going [F] round in [Em] circles And the [Am] door’s wide [G] open Boy I [F] still wanna see [Em] you Days go [Am] by, I’m still hoping, [G] hoping [F] Where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? [G] Tell me, baby, [F] where we draw the line? [Em] Tell me, baby, [Am] where we draw the line? You [F] told me to move [Em] on Searching [Am] now for somebody else But baby, [G] tell me [F] how will I find [Em] it?</description></item><item><title>Cake to Bake</title><link>http://example.org/song/2546-Arzemnieki_-_Cake_To_Bake/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 13:11:43 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2546-Arzemnieki_-_Cake_To_Bake/</guid><description>Capo 1 Intro: F Dm F Dm F I melted the ice of the polar caps Dm Found the raiders of the lost ark C Solved a case for the genius from Baker Street F Helped to clean the Central Park Dm I created the plan for the Chinese wall Gm Went to desert, made it rain Am Swam through a shark tank bloodily F Found Atlantis, by the way C But today F Bb I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Bb Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku G C Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep F I talked to a unicorn the other night Dm Took me up on a lonely star C Did the moonwalk on the milky way F Realized I&amp;#39;ve gone too far Dm So I questioned the law of gravity Gm Put the apple back up to the apple tree Am Ej tu nost: I even learned Latvian F I know it&amp;#39;s so hard to believe C But today F Bb I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C I&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Bb Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku G C Cep cep cep cep cep kuuku kuuku cep cep cep cep cep cep kuuku F Bb We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Am Bb C Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, wait for it F Am Bb C Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, wait for it F A Dm Bb Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake, have some cake F C F Mix some dough, add some love, let it bake F Bb We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and got no clue at all Gm C We&amp;#39;ve got a cake to bake, and haven&amp;#39;t done that before F A Don&amp;#39;t be proud, mate, please, don&amp;#39;t bother Dm Bb Go, come on and ask your mother F C F How to bake, how to bake, bake that cake F Garšīgi.</description></item><item><title>Heartbeat</title><link>http://example.org/song/2549-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 13:05:08 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2549-Justs_Sirmais_-_Heartbeat/</guid><description>[Am] I know you told So many times [Am] So many words In different rhymes But [D] i don’t [F] feel the [G] same [Am] I wasn’t innocent, i know [Am] And things i did for sure were wrong The [D] time has [F] passed so [G] long Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me [Am] I’m getting wild when i’m alone [Am] I learned by heart youre not my own But [D] i never [F] asked you to be[G]long [Am] Your my desire and my pain [Am] But all the battles are in vain You [D] mean more [F] than anything to [G] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me [D] You’re the one i need You’re the [F] air that i breath [D] Don’t throw my heart away I want you to [E] stay Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat Thats what i [C] want Thats what i [G] need Feeling again that youre breathing with [Am] me Feeling your [Am] heartbeat</description></item><item><title>I Wanna</title><link>http://example.org/song/2548-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_I_Wanna/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 09:02:25 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2548-Marija_Naumova_Marie_N_-_I_Wanna/</guid><description>[Am] I&amp;#39;d like to go away, but [E] it&amp;#39;s easier to say That [A m] you know all the tricks that make... that [E] make me stay [Am] I&amp;#39;m ready to support this [E] artful game you always play &amp;#39;Cause [Am] you don&amp;#39;t know the fee that you will [E] later, later pay [F] Today you think you are the winner, [C] today you think you are the king You [E] make me sweat in my emotions under your flyway, flyway [Am] wing I wanna be the [E] sunshine in your eyes, I wanna be the [Am] light from shooting stars I wanna be [E] queen in your sweetest lies, I wanna be the [Am] love-spark in your eyes I wanna be the [E] sunshine in your eyes, I wanna be the [Am] light from shooting stars I wanna be [E] queen in your sweetest lies I wanna be the love-spark in your [Am] eyes Ay ay ay ay ay ay.</description></item><item><title>Dziesma Par Laimi 3</title><link>http://example.org/song/2283-Fomins_Un_Kleins_-_Dziesma_Par_Laimi_3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jul 2015 18:11:06 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2283-Fomins_Un_Kleins_-_Dziesma_Par_Laimi_3/</guid><description>C#m akords: E------X-------------------- A------4--------------------- D------6--------------------- G------6------------------- B------5-------------------- E------4---------------------- Intro - E E Kad nav vairs nekā, Es domāju tā: C#m B A B -Man paliek vēl dziesma ko nodziedāt tev. E Par laimi ko liet, Par ceļu ko iet, C#m B A B Kā vilcieni projām pa metāla sliedēm C#m A Uz tālajām pieturām Ziemeļpolā, C#m B Kur brīvība dzīvo, bet vairāk nekā. C#m A Ik reizi , kad tālumā brīnumu jūt, A B Es vēlos vēl tuvāk tev būt!</description></item><item><title>Love injected</title><link>http://example.org/song/2175-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected/</link><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 17:42:04 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2175-Aminata_Savadogo_-_Love_Injected/</guid><description>[Em] You bring [G] the light [C] to my darkest [Am] side, babe [Em] The day, [G] the night [C] split to cure the [Am] sight, ooh [Em] You care, [G] you animate [C] You guard me bare, [Am] bring up the heart rate Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] [Em] Your eye’s a good mirror, [G] look under the cover [C] Love is above [Am] all [Em] I’m safe into your hands [G] Let’s move away, [C] the edges ex[Am]pand Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] Show me the [Em] source of the light, I’m becoming [C] affected Seeing the [Em] glow of the white is what I have de[C]tected Feeling [Em] again I’m alive, it’s your shining re[C]flected Love in[Em]jected, love in[C]jected Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] Your [Em] love revives my [C] soul And I [G] know you’ll choose it whole over[C]all [Am] [Em][G][C][Am] Oh, oh, oh, oh Oh, oh, oh, oh.</description></item><item><title>Dziesma Par Laimi 2</title><link>http://example.org/song/2028-Fomins_Un_Kleins_-_Dziesma_Par_Laimi_2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2015 12:43:15 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/2028-Fomins_Un_Kleins_-_Dziesma_Par_Laimi_2/</guid><description>Cadd11 (0 3 2 0 1 1) CAPO 3 Iespēle: C Cadd11 C Kad nav vairs nekā, es domāju tā Am Em F G Man paliek vēl dziesma ko nodziedāt tev! C Par laimi ko liet, par ceļu ko iet, F G F G Kā vilcieni projām pa metāla sliedēm, Am F Uz tālajām pieturām ziemeļpolā, Am G Kur brīvība dzīvo, bet vairāk nekā Am F Ik reizi kad tālumā brīnumu jūt, F G Es vēlos vēl tuvāk tev būt!</description></item><item><title>Hello From Mars</title><link>http://example.org/song/1711-FLY_-_Hello_From_Mars/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Aug 2014 04:05:07 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1711-FLY_-_Hello_From_Mars/</guid><description>Ievads: Dm [C] Time would have passed me by if [Em] I Had never asked you [F] why Your eyes were open [Dm] wide That [G] day you saw me [C] cry [C] I&amp;#39;m not that kind of [Em] girl Who only dreams of [F] pearls Just give me wings of [Dm] love And make it [G] real Cause [Am] I&amp;#39;m not [F] afraid Of a [Dm] blade That we [G] need to cross to[C]day But I&amp;#39;m [F] scared To be [Dm] shared By someone [G] else Cause [C] this is gonna be The [F] day that we will meet When [Dm] heaven comes so [F] down to Earth To [G] say hello from Mars Starpspēle: Am Em F Dm [C] My emotions take me [Em] high They seem to reach the [F] sky I still believe we [Dm] try To [G] hit the ground or [C] fly [Am] Life is a [G] mystery Like a [C] perfect harmo[Dm]ny [C] No one knows that [D] day when love Will [G] come and set you [A] free</description></item><item><title>Angels in disguise</title><link>http://example.org/song/1339-Musiqq_-_Angels_In_Disguise/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Sep 2011 21:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1339-Musiqq_-_Angels_In_Disguise/</guid><description>Intro: Am7 | C | G | Dm7 Am7 C G Woke up tonight, looked at the moon, Dm7 Am7 Blinding light filled up my room. C G Looked to my right – my better half, Dm7 Am7 And it’s alright, if it’s all I have, C G I let it ride, I’m satisfied, Just be mine. Chorus: Am Kill me with killa kiss, C Kill me with tempting lips, G Stare at me with candy eyes, Dm7 Love me with luscious thighs.</description></item><item><title>Dziesma Par Laimi</title><link>http://example.org/song/547-Fomins_Un_Kleins_-_Dziesma_Par_Laimi/</link><pubDate>Tue, 29 Jan 2008 22:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/547-Fomins_Un_Kleins_-_Dziesma_Par_Laimi/</guid><description>C Kad nav vairs nekā, es domāju tā, Am Em F G Man paliek vēl dziesma ko nodziedāt tev! C Am Par laimi ko liet, par ceļu ko iet, F G F G Kā vilcieni projām pa metāla sliedēm, Am F Uz tālajām pieturām ziemeļpolā, F G Kur brīvība dzīvo, bet vairāk nekā Am F Ik reizi kad tālumā brīnumu jūt, F G Es vēlos vēl tuvāk tev būt! piedz. C G Nekā ,kad nav vairs nekā, Am es vēlos tev nodziedāt, F G C Dziesmu par laimi, kas nāk, C G Kas negaidot nāk, Am Un paņem aiz rokas mūs F G Dziesma, kas būs F G C Dziesma par laimi, kas būs.</description></item></channel></rss>