<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Blitze on Latvian songs ABC notation</title><link>http://example.org/categories/blitze/</link><description>Recent content in Blitze on Latvian songs ABC notation</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:42:53 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/blitze/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hop</title><link>http://example.org/song/3367-Blitze_-_Hop/</link><pubDate>Sun, 11 Mar 2018 21:42:53 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/3367-Blitze_-_Hop/</guid><description>You look like a girlfriend I’ve never had You shine like a stars that never fall You, you, it means me You, you, it means never be free Hop, hop, hop, jump over this edge We’re not only friends where cool movie ends And hop, hop, hop, just tell me whom else Now should I suspect when in your heart There’s no respect to me Me, this is a guy who’ll never dance You will never give to me this chance Me, me, it means you Me, me, it means never be free Hop, hop, hop, jump over this edge We’re not only friends where cool movie ends And hop, hop, hop, just tell me whom else Now should I suspect when in your heart there’s… Hey baby, I’m not crazy I’m just falling in love Hop, hop, hop, jump over this edge We’re not only friends where cool movie ends And hop, hop, hop, just tell me whom else Now should I suspect when in your heart there’s… Hop, hop, hop, jump over this edge We’re not only friends where cool movie ends And hop, hop, hop, just tell me whom else Now should I suspect when in your heart There’s no respect to me</description></item><item><title>Bibliotekārs</title><link>http://example.org/song/1696-Blitze_-_Bibliotekars/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2014 04:03:47 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/song/1696-Blitze_-_Bibliotekars/</guid><description>Akordi šai dziesmai ir diezgan interesanti, nosaukumus nezinu pareizos, tāpēc apzīmēšu ar cipariem. Sorry. 1 046600 2 024400 3 022100 (E) 4 079900 1 2 E Klau cik skaisti te līst 1 2 4 Peļķēs burbuļi plīst 1 2 E Labāk palikt tepat 1 2 4 Un tos burbuļus nosargāt 1 2 E Basām kājām nāk rīts 1 2 4 Ar mūsu nakti sasaistīts 1 2 E Labāk palikt tepat 1 2 4 4 Un to kas starp mums nosargāt Piedz: How.</description></item></channel></rss>